<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.5 0.394</pos>
			<size>0.372 0.382</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.494 0.382</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.414 0.382</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.28 0.382</size>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<path>${themePath}/_inc/videos/windows.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path ifSubset="addons:yes">./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/videos/windows.mp4</path>
			<pos>0.5 0.392</pos>
			<maxSize>0.372</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.412</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.493</maxSize>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>2016</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>Amazon</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>Amazon Prime Gaming</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>Amazon Prime Gaming is a service included with an Amazon Prime subscription that provides gamers with free PC games (kept forever), exclusive in-game bonuses (such as skins and currency), and a free monthly subscription to any Twitch channel. The service, formerly known as Twitch Prime, allows users to claim content for popular games.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Amazon Prime Gaming to usługa wchodząca w skład subskrypcji Amazon Prime, oferująca graczom darmowe gry na PC (zachowywane na zawsze), ekskluzywne bonusy w grach (skórki, walutę) oraz darmową miesięczną subskrypcję dowolnego kanału Twitch. Usługa, wcześniej znana jako Twitch Prime, umożliwia otrzymywanie zawartości do popularnych gier.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Amazon Prime Gaming — это сервис, включенный в подписку Amazon Prime, предоставляющий геймерам бесплатные игры для ПК (остаются навсегда), эксклюзивные внутриигровые бонусы (скины, валюта) и бесплатную ежемесячную подписку на любой канал Twitch. Сервис, ранее известный как Twitch Prime, позволяет получать контент для популярных игр.</text>
			<text lang="es">Amazon Prime Gaming es un servicio incluido en la suscripción a Amazon Prime que ofrece a los jugadores juegos gratuitos para PC (que se conservan para siempre), bonificaciones exclusivas dentro del juego (skins, moneda) y una suscripción mensual gratuita a cualquier canal de Twitch. El servicio, anteriormente conocido como Twitch Prime, permite obtener contenido para juegos populares.</text>
			<text lang="de">Amazon Prime Gaming ist ein im Amazon-Prime-Abonnement enthaltener Dienst, der Spielern kostenlose PC-Spiele (dauerhaft behalten), exklusive In-Game-Boni (Skins, Währung) sowie ein kostenloses monatliches Abonnement für einen beliebigen Twitch-Kanal bietet. Der Dienst, früher bekannt als Twitch Prime, ermöglicht den Erhalt von Inhalten für beliebte Spiele.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Amazon Prime Gaming est un service inclus dans l’abonnement Amazon Prime qui propose aux joueurs des jeux PC gratuits (à conserver définitivement), des bonus en jeu exclusifs (skins, monnaie) ainsi qu’un abonnement mensuel gratuit à n’importe quelle chaîne Twitch. Le service, anciennement connu sous le nom de Twitch Prime, permet d’obtenir du contenu pour des jeux populaires.</text>
			<text lang="it">Amazon Prime Gaming è un servizio incluso nell’abbonamento Amazon Prime che offre ai giocatori giochi PC gratuiti (da conservare per sempre), bonus di gioco esclusivi (come skin e valuta) e un abbonamento mensile gratuito a qualsiasi canale Twitch. Il servizio, precedentemente noto come Twitch Prime, consente di ottenere contenuti per i giochi più popolari.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Amazon Prime Gaming é um serviço incluído na assinatura Amazon Prime que oferece aos jogadores jogos gratuitos para PC (mantidos para sempre), bônus exclusivos dentro dos jogos (skins, moeda) e uma assinatura mensal gratuita para qualquer canal da Twitch. O serviço, anteriormente conhecido como Twitch Prime, permite obter conteúdo para jogos populares.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
