<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<visible>false</visible>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<visible>false</visible>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>2011</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>cyxx</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>Bermuda Syndrome</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextVariant">
			<text>Port</text>
			<text lang="pl">Port</text>
			<text lang="ru">Порт</text>
			<text lang="es">Puerto</text>
			<text lang="de">Hafen</text>
			<text lang="fr">Port</text>
			<text lang="it">Port</text>
			<text lang="pt">Porto</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>Decompilation project of the Bermuda Syndrome game. This program is a re-implementation of the engine used in the game made by Century Interactive and published by BMG in 1995. This rewrite is based on the reversing of the original Windows executable.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Projekt dekompilacji gry Bermuda Syndrome. Program ten jest ponowną implementacją silnika używanego w grze stworzonej przez Century Interactive i wydanej przez BMG w 1995 roku. Przepisanie kodu oparto na inżynierii wstecznej oryginalnego pliku wykonywalnego systemu Windows.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Проект по декомпиляции игры Bermuda Syndrome. Данная программа является повторной реализацией игрового движка, использовавшегося в игре, разработанной Century Interactive и изданной BMG в 1995 году. Переписывание основано на реверс-инжиниринге оригинального исполняемого файла Windows.</text>
			<text lang="es">Proyecto de descompilación del juego Bermuda Syndrome. Este programa es una reimplementación del motor utilizado en el juego desarrollado por Century Interactive y publicado por BMG en 1995. Esta reescritura se basa en la ingeniería inversa del ejecutable original de Windows.</text>
			<text lang="de">Dekompilierungsprojekt des Spiels Bermuda Syndrome. Dieses Programm ist eine Neuimplementierung der Spiel-Engine, die im von Century Interactive entwickelten und 1995 von BMG veröffentlichten Spiel verwendet wurde. Diese Neuschreibung basiert auf Reverse Engineering der originalen Windows-Executable.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Projet de décompilation du jeu Bermuda Syndrome. Ce programme est une réimplémentation du moteur utilisé dans le jeu développé par Century Interactive et publié par BMG en 1995. Cette réécriture est basée sur l’ingénierie inverse de l’exécutable Windows original.</text>
			<text lang="it">Progetto di decompilazione del gioco Bermuda Syndrome. Questo programma è una reimplementazione del motore utilizzato nel gioco sviluppato da Century Interactive e pubblicato da BMG nel 1995. Questa riscrittura si basa sul reverse engineering dell’eseguibile originale per Windows.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Projeto de descompilação do jogo Bermuda Syndrome. Este programa é uma reimplementação do motor utilizado no jogo desenvolvido pela Century Interactive e publicado pela BMG em 1995. Esta reescrita é baseada na engenharia reversa do executável original para Windows.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
