<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.475 0.394</pos>
			<size>0.19 0.25</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.22 0.25</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.27 0.25</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.14 0.25</size>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<pos>0.475 0.394</pos>
			<maxSize>0.232</maxSize>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.472 0.394</pos>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.467 0.394</pos>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.481 0.394</pos>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>1981</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>Epoch</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>Cassette Vision</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>The Cassette Vision is a second generation home video game console made by Epoch Co. and released in Japan on July 30, 1981. A redesigned model called the Cassette Vision Jr. was released afterwards.

The term cassette is a contemporary Japanese synonym for ROM cartridge, not to be confused with the magnetic cassette tape format. In terms of power, it is comparable to the Atari 2600. The Cassette Vision has unusual controls: four knobs built into the console itself, two for each player (one for horizontal, one for vertical), plus two buttons per player.

The system originally retailed for ¥13,500, with games priced at ¥4,000. The Cassette Vision sold around 400,000 units, and was the best selling video game console in Japan before Nintendo's Family Computer. It received a successor called the Super Cassette Vision.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Cassette Vision to konsola gier wideo drugiej generacji, wyprodukowana przez Epoch Co. i wydana w Japonii 30 lipca 1981 roku. Później wydano przeprojektowany model o nazwie Cassette Vision Jr.

Termin „cassette” to współczesny japoński synonim kartridża ROM i nie należy go mylić z magnetyczną kasetą taśmową. Pod względem mocy konsola jest porównywalna do Atari 2600. Cassette Vision posiada nietypowe sterowanie: cztery pokrętła wbudowane w samą konsolę — po dwa dla każdego gracza (jedno do ruchu poziomego i jedno do pionowego) — oraz po dwa przyciski na gracza.

Początkowa cena systemu wynosiła 13 500 jenów, a gry kosztowały 4 000 jenów. Cassette Vision sprzedała się w liczbie około 400 000 egzemplarzy i była najlepiej sprzedającą się konsolą w Japonii przed pojawieniem się Nintendo Family Computer. Jej następcą była Super Cassette Vision.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Cassette Vision — это домашняя игровая приставка второго поколения, разработанная компанией Epoch Co. и выпущенная в Японии 30 июля 1981 года. Позже была выпущена переработанная модель под названием Cassette Vision Jr.

Термин «cassette» в Японии того времени обозначал картридж с ПЗУ и не имеет отношения к магнитным кассетам. По мощности система сопоставима с Atari 2600. Cassette Vision имеет необычное управление: четыре поворотных регулятора, встроенных в саму консоль — по два для каждого игрока (один для горизонтального движения и один для вертикального), а также по две кнопки на игрока.

Изначальная цена системы составляла 13 500 иен, а игры стоили около 4 000 иен. Cassette Vision была продана тиражом около 400 000 экземпляров и стала самой продаваемой игровой приставкой в Японии до появления Nintendo Family Computer. Позднее ей на смену пришла Super Cassette Vision.</text>
			<text lang="es">Cassette Vision es una consola de videojuegos doméstica de segunda generación, fabricada por Epoch Co. y lanzada en Japón el 30 de julio de 1981. Posteriormente se lanzó un modelo rediseñado llamado Cassette Vision Jr.

El término “cassette” es un sinónimo japonés contemporáneo de cartucho ROM, y no debe confundirse con las cintas magnéticas de casete. En términos de potencia, es comparable a la Atari 2600. La Cassette Vision tiene controles inusuales: cuatro perillas integradas en la propia consola, dos para cada jugador (una para el movimiento horizontal y otra para el vertical), además de dos botones por jugador.

El sistema se vendía originalmente por 13.500 yenes, y los juegos costaban 4.000 yenes. Cassette Vision vendió alrededor de 400.000 unidades y fue la consola más vendida en Japón antes de la Nintendo Family Computer. Posteriormente fue sucedida por la Super Cassette Vision.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die Cassette Vision ist eine Heimvideospielkonsole der zweiten Generation, die von Epoch Co. hergestellt und am 30. Juli 1981 in Japan veröffentlicht wurde. Später erschien ein überarbeitetes Modell namens Cassette Vision Jr.

Der Begriff „Cassette“ ist ein zeitgenössisches japanisches Synonym für ein ROM-Modul und darf nicht mit dem magnetischen Kassettenformat verwechselt werden. In Bezug auf die Leistung ist sie mit dem Atari 2600 vergleichbar. Die Cassette Vision verfügt über ungewöhnliche Bedienelemente: vier Drehregler direkt an der Konsole — zwei pro Spieler (einer für horizontale und einer für vertikale Bewegung) — sowie zwei Tasten pro Spieler.

Der ursprüngliche Verkaufspreis betrug 13.500 Yen, während Spiele etwa 4.000 Yen kosteten. Die Cassette Vision verkaufte sich rund 400.000 Mal und war vor dem Nintendo Family Computer die meistverkaufte Konsole in Japan. Ihr Nachfolger war die Super Cassette Vision.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La Cassette Vision est une console de jeux vidéo domestique de deuxième génération, fabriquée par Epoch Co. et sortie au Japon le 30 juillet 1981. Un modèle redessiné appelé Cassette Vision Jr. a été lancé par la suite.

Le terme « cassette » est un synonyme japonais contemporain de cartouche ROM et ne doit pas être confondu avec le format de cassette magnétique. En termes de puissance, elle est comparable à l’Atari 2600. La Cassette Vision possède des commandes inhabituelles : quatre molettes intégrées à la console — deux pour chaque joueur (une pour le mouvement horizontal et une pour le vertical) — ainsi que deux boutons par joueur.

Le système était initialement vendu au prix de 13 500 yens, avec des jeux à 4 000 yens. La Cassette Vision s’est vendue à environ 400 000 exemplaires et a été la console la plus vendue au Japon avant la Nintendo Family Computer. Elle a ensuite été remplacée par la Super Cassette Vision.</text>
			<text lang="it">Cassette Vision è una console per videogiochi domestica di seconda generazione, prodotta da Epoch Co. e rilasciata in Giappone il 30 luglio 1981. Successivamente è stato pubblicato un modello ridisegnato chiamato Cassette Vision Jr.

Il termine “cassette” è un sinonimo giapponese contemporaneo di cartuccia ROM e non deve essere confuso con il formato a nastro magnetico. In termini di potenza, è paragonabile all’Atari 2600. La Cassette Vision presenta controlli insoliti: quattro manopole integrate nella console stessa — due per ogni giocatore (una per il movimento orizzontale e una per quello verticale) — oltre a due pulsanti per giocatore.

Il sistema veniva inizialmente venduto a 13.500 yen, con giochi al prezzo di 4.000 yen. La Cassette Vision ha venduto circa 400.000 unità ed è stata la console più venduta in Giappone prima del Nintendo Family Computer. È stata successivamente sostituita dalla Super Cassette Vision.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O Cassette Vision é um console de videogame doméstico de segunda geração, fabricado pela Epoch Co. e lançado no Japão em 30 de julho de 1981. Posteriormente, foi lançado um modelo redesenhado chamado Cassette Vision Jr.

O termo “cassette” é um sinônimo japonês contemporâneo para cartucho ROM, não devendo ser confundido com o formato de fita cassete magnética. Em termos de potência, é comparável ao Atari 2600. O Cassette Vision possui controles incomuns: quatro botões giratórios integrados ao próprio console — dois para cada jogador (um para movimento horizontal e outro para vertical) — além de dois botões por jogador.

O sistema foi originalmente vendido por 13.500 ienes, com jogos custando 4.000 ienes. O Cassette Vision vendeu cerca de 400.000 unidades e foi o console mais vendido no Japão antes do Nintendo Family Computer. Posteriormente, foi sucedido pelo Super Cassette Vision.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
