<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.5 0.394</pos>
			<size>0.372 0.382</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.494 0.382</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.414 0.382</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.28 0.382</size>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<path>{random}</path>
			<path>${themePath}/_inc/videos/windows.mp4</path>
			<!-- Loads platform video from addon directory, if available -->
			<path ifSubset="addons:yes">./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/videos/windows.mp4</path>
			<pos>0.5 0.392</pos>
			<maxSize>0.372</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.412</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.493</maxSize>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>2011</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>Electronic Arts</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>EA Games</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>EA app (formerly Origin) is Electronic Arts’ official digital distribution platform for PC (Windows/Mac), designed for purchasing, downloading, and launching EA games. The app lets users manage their game library, install updates, save progress to the cloud, and connect with friends. EA app replaces Origin with a faster and more convenient interface.</text>
			<text lang="pl">EA app (wcześniej Origin) to oficjalna platforma dystrybucji cyfrowej firmy Electronic Arts na PC (Windows/Mac), przeznaczona do zakupu, pobierania i uruchamiania gier EA. Aplikacja umożliwia zarządzanie biblioteką gier, ich aktualizowanie, zapisywanie postępów w chmurze oraz komunikację ze znajomymi. EA app zastąpiła Origin, oferując szybszy i wygodniejszy interfejs.</text>
			<text lang="ru">EA app (ранее Origin) — это официальная платформа цифровой дистрибуции от Electronic Arts для ПК (Windows/Mac), предназначенная для покупки, загрузки и запуска игр EA. Приложение позволяет управлять библиотекой игр, обновлять их, сохранять прогресс в облаке и общаться с друзьями. EA app пришло на смену Origin, обеспечивая более быстрый и удобный интерфейс.</text>
			<text lang="es">EA app (anteriormente Origin) es la plataforma oficial de distribución digital de Electronic Arts para PC (Windows/Mac), destinada a la compra, descarga y ejecución de juegos de EA. La aplicación permite gestionar la biblioteca de juegos, actualizarlos, guardar el progreso en la nube y comunicarse con amigos. EA app reemplaza a Origin ofreciendo una interfaz más rápida y cómoda.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die EA app (ehemals Origin) ist die offizielle digitale Vertriebsplattform von Electronic Arts für PC (Windows/Mac) zum Kaufen, Herunterladen und Starten von EA-Spielen. Die Anwendung ermöglicht die Verwaltung der Spielebibliothek, das Aktualisieren von Spielen, Cloud-Speicherstände sowie die Kommunikation mit Freunden. Die EA app löst Origin ab und bietet eine schnellere und komfortablere Benutzeroberfläche.</text>
			<text lang="fr">EA app (anciennement Origin) est la plateforme officielle de distribution numérique d’Electronic Arts pour PC (Windows/Mac), destinée à l’achat, au téléchargement et au lancement des jeux EA. L’application permet de gérer sa bibliothèque de jeux, de les mettre à jour, de sauvegarder sa progression dans le cloud et de communiquer avec ses amis. EA app remplace Origin en proposant une interface plus rapide et plus pratique.</text>
			<text lang="it">EA app (precedentemente Origin) è la piattaforma ufficiale di distribuzione digitale di Electronic Arts per PC (Windows/Mac), pensata per acquistare, scaricare e avviare i giochi EA. L’app consente di gestire la libreria di giochi, aggiornarli, salvare i progressi nel cloud e comunicare con gli amici. EA app ha sostituito Origin offrendo un’interfaccia più veloce e intuitiva.</text>
			<text lang="pt">EA app (anteriormente Origin) é a plataforma oficial de distribuição digital da Electronic Arts para PC (Windows/Mac), destinada à compra, download e execução de jogos da EA. O aplicativo permite gerenciar a biblioteca de jogos, atualizá-los, salvar o progresso na nuvem e se comunicar com amigos. A EA app substituiu o Origin, oferecendo uma interface mais rápida e conveniente.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
