<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.4901 0.462</pos>
			<size>0.276 0.278</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.306 0.278</size>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.488 0.462</pos>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.368 0.278</size>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.486 0.462</pos>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.206 0.278</size>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.4921 0.462</pos>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<pos>0.4901 0.4602</pos>
			<maxSize>0.275</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.367</maxSize>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.4866 0.4602</pos>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.306</maxSize>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.4881 0.4602</pos>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.273</maxSize>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.4921 0.4602</pos>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>2021</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>shinyquagsire23</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>OpenJKDF2</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextVariant">
			<text>Port</text>
			<text lang="pl">Port</text>
			<text lang="ru">Порт</text>
			<text lang="es">Puerto</text>
			<text lang="de">Hafen</text>
			<text lang="fr">Port</text>
			<text lang="it">Port</text>
			<text lang="pt">Porto</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>OpenJKDF2 is a function-by-function reimplementation of Jedi Knight: Dark Forces II in C, with 64-bit ports to Windows 7+, macOS 10.15+, and Linux. Files are organized as closely to the original game as possible, based on symbols from the Grim Fandango Remaster Android/Linux/macOS port, as well as scattered assertions from various other games. It also contains the original versions of byacc and flex used for COG script parsing.

OpenJKDF2 added quality of life improvements to the game. This means it makes it easy to run Jedi Knight on modern machines with modern aspect ratios, monitor sizes, current generation graphic cards, and operating systems. It also now natively supports JKGFXMod—all of this simply by placing the contents of a zip file into your Jedi Knight directory!</text>
			<text lang="pl">OpenJKDF2 to reimplementacja Jedi Knight: Dark Forces II funkcja po funkcji w języku C, z 64-bitowymi portami dla Windows 7+, macOS 10.15+ oraz Linuxa. Pliki są zorganizowane możliwie najbliżej oryginalnej gry, w oparciu o symbole z portu Android/Linux/macOS Grim Fandango Remaster, a także o rozproszone asercje z innych gier. Zawiera również oryginalne wersje byacc i flex, używane do parsowania skryptów COG.

OpenJKDF2 wprowadza ulepszenia jakości życia. Oznacza to łatwe uruchamianie Jedi Knight na nowoczesnych komputerach z aktualnymi proporcjami obrazu, różnymi rozmiarami monitorów, kartami graficznymi nowej generacji oraz współczesnymi systemami operacyjnymi. Projekt oferuje także natywne wsparcie dla JKGFXMod — wszystko poprzez skopiowanie zawartości pliku ZIP do katalogu Jedi Knight.</text>
			<text lang="ru">OpenJKDF2 — это пофункциональная реимплементация Jedi Knight: Dark Forces II на языке C с 64-битными портами для Windows 7+, macOS 10.15+ и Linux. Файлы организованы максимально близко к оригинальной игре на основе символов из Android/Linux/macOS-порта Grim Fandango Remaster, а также разрозненных утверждений из других игр. Проект также включает оригинальные версии byacc и flex, использовавшиеся для разбора COG-скриптов.

OpenJKDF2 так же добавляет улучшения, повышающие удобство использования игры. Это упрощает запуск Jedi Knight на современных компьютерах с актуальными соотношениями сторон, размерами мониторов, видеокартами нового поколения и современными операционными системами. Также теперь нативно поддерживается JKGFXMod — всё это достигается простым копированием содержимого ZIP-архива в каталог Jedi Knight.</text>
			<text lang="es">OpenJKDF2 es una reimplementación función por función de Jedi Knight: Dark Forces II en C, con versiones de 64 bits para Windows 7+, macOS 10.15+ y Linux. Los archivos están organizados lo más fielmente posible al juego original, basándose en símbolos del port Android/Linux/macOS de Grim Fandango Remaster, así como en diversas aserciones dispersas de otros juegos. También incluye las versiones originales de byacc y flex utilizadas para el análisis de scripts COG.

OpenJKDF2 añadió mejoras de calidad de vida al juego. Esto facilita ejecutar Jedi Knight en equipos modernos con relaciones de aspecto actuales, distintos tamaños de monitor, tarjetas gráficas de última generación y sistemas operativos modernos. Además, ahora es compatible de forma nativa con JKGFXMod — todo ello simplemente copiando el contenido de un archivo ZIP en el directorio de Jedi Knight.</text>
			<text lang="de">OpenJKDF2 ist eine Funktions-für-Funktions-Neuimplementierung von Jedi Knight: Dark Forces II in C mit 64-Bit-Ports für Windows 7+, macOS 10.15+ und Linux. Die Dateien sind so nah wie möglich am Originalspiel organisiert, basierend auf Symbolen aus dem Android/Linux/macOS-Port von Grim Fandango Remaster sowie auf verstreuten Assertions aus verschiedenen anderen Spielen. Zudem enthält es die originalen Versionen von byacc und flex, die für das Parsen der COG-Skripte verwendet wurden.

OpenJKDF2 hat Komfortverbesserungen (Quality-of-Life) zum Spiel hinzugefügt. Dadurch lässt sich Jedi Knight problemlos auf modernen Systemen mit aktuellen Seitenverhältnissen, verschiedenen Monitorgrößen, Grafikkarten der neuesten Generation und modernen Betriebssystemen ausführen. Außerdem wird JKGFXMod nun nativ unterstützt — alles, indem man einfach den Inhalt einer ZIP-Datei in das Jedi Knight-Verzeichnis kopiert.</text>
			<text lang="fr">OpenJKDF2 est une réimplémentation fonction par fonction de Jedi Knight: Dark Forces II en C, avec des ports 64 bits pour Windows 7+, macOS 10.15+ et Linux. Les fichiers sont organisés aussi fidèlement que possible au jeu original, en s’appuyant sur les symboles du port Android/Linux/macOS de Grim Fandango Remaster, ainsi que sur diverses assertions dispersées provenant d’autres jeux. Il inclut également les versions originales de byacc et flex utilisées pour l’analyse des scripts COG.

OpenJKDF2 a ajouté des améliorations de confort de jeu. Cela signifie qu’il facilite l’exécution de Jedi Knight sur des machines modernes avec des formats d’image actuels, différentes tailles d’écrans, des cartes graphiques de nouvelle génération et des systèmes d’exploitation modernes. Il prend désormais en charge nativement JKGFXMod — le tout simplement en plaçant le contenu d’un fichier ZIP dans le répertoire de Jedi Knight.</text>
			<text lang="it">OpenJKDF2 è una reimplementazione funzione per funzione di Jedi Knight: Dark Forces II in C, con porting a 64 bit per Windows 7+, macOS 10.15+ e Linux. I file sono organizzati il più fedelmente possibile al gioco originale, basandosi sui simboli della versione Android/Linux/macOS di Grim Fandango Remaster, oltre a varie asserzioni sparse provenienti da altri giochi. Include inoltre le versioni originali di byacc e flex utilizzate per il parsing degli script COG.

OpenJKDF2 ha introdotto miglioramenti alla qualità della vita del gioco. Questo significa che rende semplice eseguire Jedi Knight su macchine moderne con rapporti d’aspetto moderni, diverse dimensioni di monitor, schede grafiche di ultima generazione e sistemi operativi attuali. Ora supporta anche nativamente JKGFXMod — tutto semplicemente copiando il contenuto di un file ZIP nella directory di Jedi Knight.</text>
			<text lang="pt">OpenJKDF2 é uma reimplementação função por função de Jedi Knight: Dark Forces II em C, com versões de 64 bits para Windows 7+, macOS 10.15+ e Linux. Os arquivos são organizados o mais próximo possível do jogo original, com base em símbolos do port Android/Linux/macOS de Grim Fandango Remaster, bem como em diversas asserções dispersas de outros jogos. Também inclui as versões originais de byacc e flex usadas para o parsing de scripts COG.

O OpenJKDF2 adicionou melhorias de qualidade de vida ao jogo. Isso facilita executar Jedi Knight em máquinas modernas com proporções de tela atuais, diferentes tamanhos de monitor, placas gráficas de última geração e sistemas operacionais modernos. Ele também oferece suporte nativo ao JKGFXMod — tudo isso simplesmente colocando o conteúdo de um arquivo ZIP no diretório de Jedi Knight.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
