<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.475 0.394</pos>
			<size>0.19 0.25</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.22 0.25</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.27 0.25</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.14 0.25</size>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<pos>0.475 0.394</pos>
			<maxSize>0.232</maxSize>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.472 0.394</pos>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.467 0.394</pos>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.481 0.394</pos>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>1983</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>Tandy / RadioShack</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>TRS-80 MC-10</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>The TRS-80 MC-10 microcomputer is a lesser-known member of the TRS-80 line of home computers, produced by Tandy Corporation in the early 1980s and sold through their RadioShack and Tandy chains of electronics stores. It was a low-cost alternative to Tandy's own TRS-80 Color Computer to compete with entry-level machines such as the VIC-20 and Sinclair ZX81.

The MC-10 was of value primarily to hobbyists and as an introduction to computer programming. It was not a commercial success and was discontinued only a year after its introduction.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Mikrokomputer TRS-80 MC-10 to mniej znany przedstawiciel linii komputerów domowych TRS-80, produkowany przez Tandy Corporation na początku lat 80. i sprzedawany za pośrednictwem sieci sklepów elektronicznych RadioShack i Tandy. Został zaprojektowany jako tania alternatywa dla TRS-80 Color Computer firmy Tandy, konkurując z podstawowymi maszynami takimi jak VIC-20 i Sinclair ZX81.

MC-10 był skierowany głównie do hobbystów oraz jako wprowadzenie do programowania. Nie odniósł sukcesu komercyjnego i został wycofany z rynku już rok po premierze.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Микрокомпьютер TRS-80 MC-10 — это малоизвестный представитель линейки домашних компьютеров TRS-80, производившийся компанией Tandy Corporation в начале 1980-х годов и продававшийся через сети магазинов электроники RadioShack и Tandy. Он задумывался как недорогая альтернатива собственному TRS-80 Color Computer от Tandy, конкурируя с базовыми машинами, такими как VIC-20 и Sinclair ZX81.

MC-10 представлял интерес главным образом для энтузиастов и как средство для обучения программированию. Он не имел коммерческого успеха и был снят с производства всего через год после выхода.</text>
			<text lang="es">El microordenador TRS-80 MC-10 es un miembro menos conocido de la línea de ordenadores domésticos TRS-80, producido por Tandy Corporation a principios de la década de 1980 y vendido a través de las cadenas de tiendas de electrónica RadioShack y Tandy. Fue diseñado como una alternativa de bajo costo al TRS-80 Color Computer de Tandy, compitiendo con máquinas de nivel de entrada como el VIC-20 y el Sinclair ZX81.

El MC-10 fue principalmente de interés para aficionados y como introducción a la programación. No tuvo éxito comercial y fue descontinuado apenas un año después de su lanzamiento.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Mikrocomputer TRS-80 MC-10 ist ein weniger bekanntes Mitglied der TRS-80-Heimcomputerreihe, hergestellt von der Tandy Corporation in den frühen 1980er Jahren und über die Elektronikhandelsketten RadioShack und Tandy vertrieben. Er wurde als kostengünstige Alternative zum TRS-80 Color Computer von Tandy entwickelt und konkurrierte mit Einsteigermodellen wie dem VIC-20 und dem Sinclair ZX81.

Der MC-10 war hauptsächlich für Hobbyisten gedacht und als Einstieg in die Programmierung geeignet. Er war kein kommerzieller Erfolg und wurde bereits ein Jahr nach seiner Einführung wieder eingestellt.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le micro-ordinateur TRS-80 MC-10 est un membre moins connu de la gamme d’ordinateurs domestiques TRS-80, produit par Tandy Corporation au début des années 1980 et vendu via les chaînes de magasins d’électronique RadioShack et Tandy. Il a été conçu comme une alternative à bas coût au TRS-80 Color Computer de Tandy, en concurrence avec des machines d’entrée de gamme telles que le VIC-20 et le Sinclair ZX81.

Le MC-10 intéressait בעיקר les amateurs et servait d’introduction à la programmation informatique. Il n’a pas rencontré de succès commercial et a été abandonné seulement un an après son lancement.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il microcomputer TRS-80 MC-10 è un membro meno noto della linea di computer domestici TRS-80, prodotto dalla Tandy Corporation nei primi anni ’80 e venduto attraverso le catene di negozi di elettronica RadioShack e Tandy. Fu progettato come alternativa a basso costo al TRS-80 Color Computer di Tandy, in competizione con macchine entry-level come il VIC-20 e il Sinclair ZX81.

Il MC-10 era destinato principalmente agli appassionati e come introduzione alla programmazione. Non ebbe successo commerciale e fu ritirato dal mercato solo un anno dopo il suo lancio.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O microcomputador TRS-80 MC-10 é um membro menos conhecido da linha de computadores domésticos TRS-80, produzido pela Tandy Corporation no início da década de 1980 e vendido através das cadeias de lojas de eletrónica RadioShack e Tandy. Foi concebido como uma alternativa de baixo custo ao TRS-80 Color Computer da própria Tandy, competindo com máquinas de entrada como o VIC-20 e o Sinclair ZX81.

O MC-10 era voltado principalmente para entusiastas e como introdução à programação. Não teve sucesso comercial e foi descontinuado apenas um ano após o seu lançamento.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
