<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.489 0.463</pos>
			<size>0.276 0.28</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.368 0.28</size>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.4858 0.463</pos>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.306 0.28</size>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.488 0.463</pos>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.206 0.28</size>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.492 0.463</pos>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<pos>0.489 0.4606</pos>
			<maxSize>0.27</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.36</maxSize>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.4858 0.4606</pos>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.30</maxSize>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.488 0.4606</pos>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.492 0.4606</pos>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>2023</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>openmoh</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>OpenMoHAA</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextVariant">
			<text>Port</text>
			<text lang="pl">Port</text>
			<text lang="ru">Порт</text>
			<text lang="es">Puerto</text>
			<text lang="de">Hafen</text>
			<text lang="fr">Port</text>
			<text lang="it">Port</text>
			<text lang="pt">Porto</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>OpenMoHAA is an open-source project aimed at preserving and enhancing Medal of Honor: Allied Assault (including Spearhead and Breakthrough expansions) by providing more features and bugfixes, across modern platforms and architectures.

Powered by ioquake3 and the F.A.K.K SDK, OpenMoHAA provides:
• Full compatibility with the original game: assets, scripts and multiplayer
• Better support for modern systems
• Cross-platform support (Linux, Windows, macOS)
• Support for both single-player and multiplayer modes
• Includes all fixes from Spearhead 2.15 and Breakthrough 2.40b
• More fixes and features, such as bots and a ban system</text>
			<text lang="pl">OpenMoHAA to projekt open-source, którego celem jest zachowanie i rozwijanie Medal of Honor: Allied Assault (wraz z dodatkami Spearhead i Breakthrough), oferujący więcej funkcji i poprawek błędów na nowoczesnych platformach i architekturach.

Oparty na ioquake3 oraz SDK F.A.K.K, OpenMoHAA oferuje:
• Pełną kompatybilność z oryginalną grą: zasoby, skrypty i tryb wieloosobowy
• Lepsze wsparcie dla nowoczesnych systemów
• Obsługę wieloplatformową (Linux, Windows, macOS)
• Wsparcie dla trybu jednoosobowego i wieloosobowego
• Zawiera wszystkie poprawki ze Spearhead 2.15 oraz Breakthrough 2.40b
• Dodatkowe poprawki i funkcje, takie jak boty i system banów</text>
			<text lang="ru">OpenMoHAA — это проект с открытым исходным кодом, направленный на сохранение и улучшение Medal of Honor: Allied Assault (включая дополнения Spearhead и Breakthrough), предоставляющий больше возможностей и исправлений ошибок на современных платформах и архитектурах.

Основанный на ioquake3 и SDK F.A.K.K, OpenMoHAA предлагает:
• Полную совместимость с оригинальной игрой: ресурсы, скрипты и мультиплеер
• Улучшенную поддержку современных систем
• Кроссплатформенную поддержку (Linux, Windows, macOS)
• Поддержку одиночного и многопользовательского режимов
• Включает все исправления из Spearhead 2.15 и Breakthrough 2.40b
• Дополнительные исправления и функции, такие как боты и система банов</text>
			<text lang="es">OpenMoHAA es un proyecto de código abierto cuyo objetivo es preservar y mejorar Medal of Honor: Allied Assault (incluidas las expansiones Spearhead y Breakthrough), ofreciendo más funciones y correcciones de errores en plataformas y arquitecturas modernas.

Impulsado por ioquake3 y el SDK F.A.K.K, OpenMoHAA ofrece:
• Compatibilidad total con el juego original: recursos, scripts y multijugador
• Mejor soporte para sistemas modernos
• Soporte multiplataforma (Linux, Windows, macOS)
• Compatibilidad con modos de un jugador y multijugador
• Incluye todas las correcciones de Spearhead 2.15 y Breakthrough 2.40b
• Más correcciones y funciones, como bots y un sistema de baneos</text>
			<text lang="de">OpenMoHAA ist ein Open-Source-Projekt zur Erhaltung und Verbesserung von Medal of Honor: Allied Assault (einschließlich der Erweiterungen Spearhead und Breakthrough) und bietet zusätzliche Funktionen sowie Fehlerbehebungen für moderne Plattformen und Architekturen.

Angetrieben von ioquake3 und dem F.A.K.K SDK bietet OpenMoHAA:
• Volle Kompatibilität mit dem Originalspiel: Assets, Skripte und Mehrspieler
• Bessere Unterstützung moderner Systeme
• Plattformübergreifende Unterstützung (Linux, Windows, macOS)
• Unterstützung für Einzelspieler- und Mehrspielermodus
• Enthält alle Fixes aus Spearhead 2.15 und Breakthrough 2.40b
• Weitere Fehlerbehebungen und Funktionen wie Bots und ein Bannsystem</text>
			<text lang="fr">OpenMoHAA est un projet open source visant à préserver et améliorer Medal of Honor: Allied Assault (y compris les extensions Spearhead et Breakthrough), en apportant davantage de fonctionnalités et de corrections de bugs sur les plateformes et architectures modernes.

Propulsé par ioquake3 et le SDK F.A.K.K, OpenMoHAA propose :
• Compatibilité totale avec le jeu original : ressources, scripts et multijoueur
• Meilleure prise en charge des systèmes modernes
• Support multiplateforme (Linux, Windows, macOS)
• Prise en charge des modes solo et multijoueur
• Inclut tous les correctifs de Spearhead 2.15 et Breakthrough 2.40b
• Davantage de correctifs et de fonctionnalités, comme des bots et un système de bannissement</text>
			<text lang="it">OpenMoHAA è un progetto open-source che mira a preservare e migliorare Medal of Honor: Allied Assault (incluse le espansioni Spearhead e Breakthrough), offrendo più funzionalità e correzioni di bug su piattaforme e architetture moderne.

Basato su ioquake3 e sull’SDK F.A.K.K, OpenMoHAA offre:
• Compatibilità completa con il gioco originale: asset, script e multiplayer
• Migliore supporto per i sistemi moderni
• Supporto multipiattaforma (Linux, Windows, macOS)
• Supporto sia per la modalità giocatore singolo che multigiocatore
• Include tutte le correzioni di Spearhead 2.15 e Breakthrough 2.40b
• Ulteriori correzioni e funzionalità, come bot e sistema di ban</text>
			<text lang="pt">OpenMoHAA é um projeto de código aberto com o objetivo de preservar e aprimorar Medal of Honor: Allied Assault (incluindo as expansões Spearhead e Breakthrough), oferecendo mais recursos e correções de bugs em plataformas e arquiteturas modernas.

Baseado no ioquake3 e no SDK F.A.K.K, o OpenMoHAA oferece:
• Compatibilidade total com o jogo original: assets, scripts e modo multiplayer
• Melhor suporte para sistemas modernos
• Suporte multiplataforma (Linux, Windows, macOS)
• Suporte aos modos single-player e multiplayer
• Inclui todas as correções do Spearhead 2.15 e Breakthrough 2.40b
• Mais correções e recursos, como bots e um sistema de banimento</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
