<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-left">
			<pos>0.305 0.45</pos>
			<size>0.1 0.3</size>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.95 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.64 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.14 0.5</origin>
			<visible>true</visible>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-right">
			<pos>0.695 0.45</pos>
			<size>0.1 0.3</size>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.04 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.36 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.86 0.5</origin>
			<visible>true</visible>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.499 0.47</pos>
			<size>0.32 0.22</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.36 0.22</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.42 0.22</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.27 0.22</size>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<pos>0.4994 0.47</pos>
			<maxSize>0.3</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.34</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.41</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.23</maxSize>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>2007</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>Namco</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>System 3xx</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>The Namco System 357 is an arcade system board based on the Sony PlayStation 3. It was released in 2007 as the board for Tekken 6. Unlike its predecessor, it did not see widespread adoption by other manufacturers.

In 2011, Namco released an upgraded version of the arcade board, the System 369, also known as System 359, for use with Tekken Tag Tournament 2. The System 369's specifications are the same as Slim model retail PS3 consoles, and as such feature a smaller chassis with less heat.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Namco System 357 to płyta systemowa arcade oparta na konsoli Sony PlayStation 3. Została wydana w 2007 roku jako platforma dla gry Tekken 6. W przeciwieństwie do swojego poprzednika, nie zdobyła szerokiego zastosowania wśród innych producentów.

W 2011 roku Namco wydało ulepszoną wersję tej płyty arcade — System 369, znaną również jako System 359 — przeznaczoną do gry Tekken Tag Tournament 2. Specyfikacja Systemu 369 jest taka sama jak w konsolach PS3 Slim dostępnych w sprzedaży, dlatego posiada mniejszą obudowę i generuje mniej ciepła.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Namco System 357 — это аркадная системная плата, основанная на Sony PlayStation 3. Она была выпущена в 2007 году как платформа для Tekken 6. В отличие от своего предшественника, она не получила широкого распространения среди других производителей.

В 2011 году Namco выпустила улучшенную версию этой аркадной платы — System 369, также известную как System 359 — для использования с Tekken Tag Tournament 2. Характеристики System 369 соответствуют розничным консолям PS3 Slim, благодаря чему она имеет более компактный корпус и выделяет меньше тепла.</text>
			<text lang="es">Namco System 357 es una placa de sistema arcade basada en la Sony PlayStation 3. Fue lanzada en 2007 como plataforma para Tekken 6. A diferencia de su predecesora, no tuvo una adopción generalizada por parte de otros fabricantes.

En 2011, Namco lanzó una versión mejorada de la placa arcade, la System 369, también conocida como System 359, para su uso con Tekken Tag Tournament 2. Las especificaciones de la System 369 son iguales a las de las consolas PS3 Slim de venta al público, por lo que cuenta con un chasis más pequeño y genera menos calor.</text>
			<text lang="de">Das Namco System 357 ist eine Arcade-Systemplatine, die auf der Sony PlayStation 3 basiert. Es wurde 2007 als Plattform für Tekken 6 veröffentlicht. Im Gegensatz zu seinem Vorgänger fand es keine weite Verbreitung bei anderen Herstellern.

Im Jahr 2011 veröffentlichte Namco eine verbesserte Version der Arcade-Platine, das System 369, auch bekannt als System 359, für den Einsatz mit Tekken Tag Tournament 2. Die Spezifikationen des System 369 entsprechen denen der im Handel erhältlichen PS3-Slim-Konsolen, weshalb es ein kleineres Gehäuse besitzt und weniger Wärme erzeugt.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Namco System 357 est une carte système d’arcade basée sur la Sony PlayStation 3. Elle a été lancée en 2007 comme plateforme pour Tekken 6. Contrairement à son prédécesseur, elle n’a pas connu une adoption généralisée par d’autres fabricants.

En 2011, Namco a lancé une version améliorée de la carte arcade, le System 369, également connu sous le nom de System 359, destinée à Tekken Tag Tournament 2. Les spécifications du System 369 sont identiques à celles des consoles PS3 Slim vendues dans le commerce, ce qui lui permet d’avoir un châssis plus compact et de produire moins de chaleur.</text>
			<text lang="it">Namco System 357 è una scheda arcade basata sulla Sony PlayStation 3. È stata rilasciata nel 2007 come piattaforma per Tekken 6. A differenza del suo predecessore, non ha avuto un’adozione diffusa da parte di altri produttori.

Nel 2011, Namco ha rilasciato una versione aggiornata della scheda arcade, la System 369, nota anche come System 359, per l’uso con Tekken Tag Tournament 2. Le specifiche della System 369 sono le stesse delle console PS3 Slim in commercio, e quindi presenta un chassis più piccolo e una minore produzione di calore.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O Namco System 357 é uma placa de sistema arcade baseada no Sony PlayStation 3. Foi lançado em 2007 como plataforma para Tekken 6. Ao contrário do seu antecessor, não teve uma adoção generalizada por outros fabricantes.

Em 2011, a Namco lançou uma versão atualizada da placa arcade, o System 369, também conhecido como System 359, para uso com Tekken Tag Tournament 2. As especificações do System 369 são iguais às dos consoles PS3 Slim vendidos no varejo, e, por isso, possui um chassis menor e gera menos calor.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
