<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.47 0.354</pos>
			<size>0.18 0.24</size>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.468 0.354</pos>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.2 0.24</size>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.46 0.354</pos>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.24 0.24</size>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.48 0.354</pos>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.14 0.24</size>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<pos>0.468 0.36</pos>
			<maxSize>0.21</maxSize>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.465 0.36</pos>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.458 0.36</pos>
			<pos if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.4762 0.36</pos>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>1979</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>NEC</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>PC-8001</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>The PC-8000 series is a line of personal computers developed by NEC for the Japanese market and became one of the most popular personal computers in the country during the early 1980s. It featured a NEC µPD780C CPU compatible with the Zilog Z80, running at 4 MHz, 16–32 KB of RAM, and a Microsoft N-BASIC interpreter in ROM. The PC-8001 series includes the models PC-8001 (1979), PC-8001 mkII (1983), and PC-8001 mkII SR (1985). The PC-8001 model was also sold in the United States and Canada as the PC-8001A.

Original models of the NEC PC-8001B (sometimes referred to as the NEC PC-8000) were also distributed in several European countries, including the United Kingdom, France, Spain, Italy, and the Netherlands, as well as in Australia and New Zealand.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Seria PC-8000 to linia komputerów osobistych opracowanych przez NEC na rynek japoński, która stała się jedną z najpopularniejszych w kraju na początku lat 80. Komputery te były wyposażone w procesor NEC µPD780C kompatybilny z Zilog Z80 o częstotliwości 4 MHz, 16–32 KB pamięci RAM oraz interpreter Microsoft N-BASIC w pamięci ROM. Seria PC-8001 obejmuje modele PC-8001 (1979), PC-8001 mkII (1983) oraz PC-8001 mkII SR (1985). Model PC-8001 był również sprzedawany w Stanach Zjednoczonych i Kanadzie jako PC-8001A.

Oryginalne modele NEC PC-8001B (czasami określane jako NEC PC-8000) były także dystrybuowane w kilku krajach europejskich, w tym w Wielkiej Brytanii, Francji, Hiszpanii, Włoszech i Holandii, a także w Australii i Nowej Zelandii.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Серия PC-8000 — это линейка персональных компьютеров, разработанных компанией NEC для японского рынка, которая стала одной из самых популярных в стране в начале 1980-х годов. Компьютеры оснащались процессором NEC µPD780C, совместимым с Zilog Z80, с тактовой частотой 4 МГц, 16–32 КБ оперативной памяти и интерпретатором Microsoft N-BASIC в ПЗУ. В серию PC-8001 входят модели PC-8001 (1979), PC-8001 mkII (1983) и PC-8001 mkII SR (1985). Модель PC-8001 также продавалась в США и Канаде под названием PC-8001A.

Оригинальные модели NEC PC-8001B (иногда называемые NEC PC-8000) также поставлялись в ряд европейских стран, включая Великобританию, Францию, Испанию, Италию и Нидерланды, а также в Австралию и Новую Зеландию.</text>
			<text lang="es">La serie PC-8000 es una línea de ordenadores personales desarrollada por NEC para el mercado japonés, que se convirtió en una de las más populares del país a principios de los años 80. Estos equipos contaban con una CPU NEC µPD780C compatible con Zilog Z80 a 4 MHz, 16–32 KB de RAM y un intérprete Microsoft N-BASIC en ROM. La serie PC-8001 incluye los modelos PC-8001 (1979), PC-8001 mkII (1983) y PC-8001 mkII SR (1985). El modelo PC-8001 también se vendió en Estados Unidos y Canadá como PC-8001A.

Los modelos originales NEC PC-8001B (a veces denominados NEC PC-8000) también se distribuyeron en varios países europeos, incluyendo Reino Unido, Francia, España, Italia y los Países Bajos, así como en Australia y Nueva Zelanda.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die PC-8000-Serie ist eine Reihe von Personal Computern, die von NEC für den japanischen Markt entwickelt wurde und Anfang der 1980er Jahre zu den beliebtesten Computern im Land gehörte. Sie waren mit einem NEC µPD780C-Prozessor ausgestattet, der mit dem Zilog Z80 kompatibel ist und mit 4 MHz arbeitet, sowie mit 16–32 KB RAM und einem Microsoft N-BASIC-Interpreter im ROM. Zur PC-8001-Serie gehören die Modelle PC-8001 (1979), PC-8001 mkII (1983) und PC-8001 mkII SR (1985). Das Modell PC-8001 wurde auch in den USA und Kanada als PC-8001A verkauft.

Die ursprünglichen Modelle des NEC PC-8001B (manchmal auch als NEC PC-8000 bezeichnet) wurden außerdem in mehreren europäischen Ländern vertrieben, darunter Großbritannien, Frankreich, Spanien, Italien und die Niederlande, sowie in Australien und Neuseeland.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La série PC-8000 est une gamme d’ordinateurs personnels développée par NEC pour le marché japonais, qui est devenue l’une des plus populaires du pays au début des années 1980. Ces ordinateurs étaient équipés d’un processeur NEC µPD780C compatible avec le Zilog Z80 à 4 MHz, de 16 à 32 Ko de RAM et d’un interpréteur Microsoft N-BASIC en ROM. La série PC-8001 comprend les modèles PC-8001 (1979), PC-8001 mkII (1983) et PC-8001 mkII SR (1985). Le modèle PC-8001 a également été vendu aux États-Unis et au Canada sous le nom de PC-8001A.

Les modèles originaux NEC PC-8001B (parfois appelés NEC PC-8000) ont également été distribués dans plusieurs pays européens, notamment au Royaume-Uni, en France, en Espagne, en Italie et aux Pays-Bas, ainsi qu’en Australie et en Nouvelle-Zélande.</text>
			<text lang="it">La serie PC-8000 è una linea di personal computer sviluppata da NEC per il mercato giapponese, che divenne una delle più popolari nel paese all’inizio degli anni ’80. I computer erano dotati di una CPU NEC µPD780C compatibile con Zilog Z80 a 4 MHz, 16–32 KB di RAM e un interprete Microsoft N-BASIC in ROM. La serie PC-8001 include i modelli PC-8001 (1979), PC-8001 mkII (1983) e PC-8001 mkII SR (1985). Il modello PC-8001 è stato venduto anche negli Stati Uniti e in Canada con il nome PC-8001A.

I modelli originali NEC PC-8001B (talvolta indicati come NEC PC-8000) sono stati distribuiti anche in diversi paesi europei, tra cui Regno Unito, Francia, Spagna, Italia e Paesi Bassi, oltre che in Australia e Nuova Zelanda.</text>
			<text lang="pt">A série PC-8000 é uma linha de computadores pessoais desenvolvida pela NEC para o mercado japonês, que se tornou uma das mais populares no país no início da década de 1980. Estes computadores eram equipados com um processador NEC µPD780C compatível com o Zilog Z80 a 4 MHz, 16–32 KB de RAM e um interpretador Microsoft N-BASIC em ROM. A série PC-8001 inclui os modelos PC-8001 (1979), PC-8001 mkII (1983) e PC-8001 mkII SR (1985). O modelo PC-8001 também foi vendido nos Estados Unidos e no Canadá como PC-8001A.

Os modelos originais NEC PC-8001B (por vezes referidos como NEC PC-8000) também foram distribuídos em vários países europeus, incluindo Reino Unido, França, Espanha, Itália e Países Baixos, bem como na Austrália e Nova Zelândia.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
