<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.5 0.41</pos>
			<size>0.35 0.35</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.39 0.35</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.47 0.35</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.264 0.35</size>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<pos>0.5 0.41</pos>
			<maxSize>0.351</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.391</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.47</maxSize>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>2013</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>Jei</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>Power Bomberman</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextVariant">
			<text>FanGame</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>Power Bomberman is a fan-made game, created as a tribute to the classic Bomberman series. It combines fast-paced strategic gameplay with enhancements such as new mechanics, a wide variety of characters, and extensive customization options, while preserving the original charm of block-blasting explosions and rivalry.

• Frantic gameplay up to 12 players
• Battle Mode includes Quick Battle, Local Battle and Online Battle
• 6 different Battle Mode rules - Survival Battle, Reversi Battle, Dodge Battle, Hyper Bomber, King Battle, Battle Royale
• Score Mode - a remake of NES Bomberman game, also including an amped-up Turbo mode
• Plethora of different items, many of which you already know and love, some never seen before
• Over 700 unlockable playable characters from series' entire lifespan, along with some Konami guests
• Over 80 stages, totaling around 700 variants to play on
• Many different settings, from Revenge Bomber and Sudden Death known from the original games to more in-depth ones like bomb fuse, explosion timing or damage caused by the Pressure Blocks
• and more!</text>
			<text lang="it">Power Bomberman è un gioco fan-made, creato come tributo alla classica serie Bomberman. Combina un gameplay strategico frenetico con miglioramenti come nuove meccaniche, una grande varietà di personaggi e ampie opzioni di personalizzazione, preservando il fascino originale delle esplosioni e della rivalità.

• Gameplay frenetico fino a 12 giocatori
• La modalità Battaglia include Battaglia Rapida, Battaglia Locale e Battaglia Online
• 6 diverse regole della modalità Battaglia: Survival Battle, Reversi Battle, Dodge Battle, Hyper Bomber, King Battle, Battle Royale
• Modalità Punteggio — remake del Bomberman per NES, con anche una modalità Turbo potenziata
• Una miriade di oggetti diversi, molti dei quali già conosci e ami, altri mai visti prima
• Oltre 700 personaggi giocabili sbloccabili provenienti dall’intera storia della serie, inclusi alcuni ospiti Konami
• Oltre 80 livelli, per un totale di circa 700 varianti giocabili
• Numerose impostazioni, da Revenge Bomber e Sudden Death dei giochi originali a opzioni più avanzate come la miccia delle bombe, il tempo delle esplosioni o i danni causati dai Pressure Blocks
• e molto altro!</text>
			<text lang="fr">Power Bomberman est un jeu créé par des fans, conçu comme un hommage à la série classique Bomberman. Il combine un gameplay stratégique frénétique avec des améliorations telles que de nouvelles mécaniques, une grande variété de personnages et de vastes options de personnalisation, tout en préservant le charme original des explosions et de la rivalité.

• Gameplay frénétique jusqu’à 12 joueurs
• Le mode Combat comprend Combat Rapide, Combat Local et Combat en Ligne
• 6 règles différentes pour le mode Combat : Survival Battle, Reversi Battle, Dodge Battle, Hyper Bomber, King Battle, Battle Royale
• Mode Score — remake du Bomberman NES, incluant également un mode Turbo survitaminé
• Une multitude d’objets variés, dont beaucoup que vous connaissez et aimez déjà, ainsi que d’autres totalement inédits
• Plus de 700 personnages jouables déblocables issus de toute l’histoire de la série, avec quelques invités Konami
• Plus de 80 niveaux, totalisant environ 700 variantes jouables
• De nombreux réglages, des classiques Revenge Bomber et Mort Subite aux options plus avancées comme la durée de la mèche, le timing des explosions ou les dégâts causés par les blocs de pression
• et bien plus encore!</text>
			<text lang="de">Power Bomberman ist ein Fan-Spiel, das als Hommage an die klassische Bomberman-Reihe entwickelt wurde. Es kombiniert rasantes, strategisches Gameplay mit Verbesserungen wie neuen Mechaniken, einer großen Auswahl an Charakteren und umfangreichen Anpassungsoptionen, während der ursprüngliche Charme von Explosionen und Rivalität erhalten bleibt.

• Rasantes Gameplay für bis zu 12 Spieler
• Der Kampfmodus umfasst Schnellkampf, Lokalen Kampf und Online-Kampf
• 6 verschiedene Kampfmodus-Regeln: Survival Battle, Reversi Battle, Dodge Battle, Hyper Bomber, King Battle, Battle Royale
• Punktmodus — ein Remake des NES-Bomberman, inklusive eines verstärkten Turbo-Modus
• Eine Vielzahl unterschiedlicher Items, viele davon bekannt und beliebt, andere völlig neu
• Über 700 freischaltbare spielbare Charaktere aus der gesamten Geschichte der Serie, einschließlich einiger Konami-Gäste
• Über 80 Levels mit insgesamt rund 700 spielbaren Varianten
• Zahlreiche Einstellungen, von Revenge Bomber und Sudden Death aus den Originalspielen bis hin zu detaillierteren Optionen wie Bombenzündschnur, Explosions-Timing oder Schaden durch Pressure Blocks
• und vieles mehr!</text>
			<text lang="es">Power Bomberman es un juego creado por fans como homenaje a la clásica serie Bomberman. Combina un gameplay estratégico y frenético con mejoras como nuevas mecánicas, una gran variedad de personajes y amplias opciones de personalización, manteniendo el encanto original de las explosiones y la rivalidad.

• Jugabilidad frenética para hasta 12 jugadores
• El modo Batalla incluye Batalla Rápida, Batalla Local y Batalla Online
• 6 reglas diferentes del modo Batalla: Survival Battle, Reversi Battle, Dodge Battle, Hyper Bomber, King Battle, Battle Royale
• Modo Puntuación — un remake del Bomberman de NES, que también incluye un modo Turbo potenciado
• Gran cantidad de objetos distintos, muchos ya conocidos y queridos, y otros nunca vistos
• Más de 700 personajes jugables desbloqueables de toda la historia de la serie, junto con algunos invitados de Konami
• Más de 80 escenarios, con un total de unas 700 variantes jugables
• Muchas opciones de configuración, desde Revenge Bomber y Muerte Súbita de los juegos originales hasta ajustes más avanzados como la mecha de las bombas, el tiempo de explosión o el daño causado por los bloques de presión
• ¡y mucho más!</text>
			<text lang="ru">Power Bomberman — фанатская игра, созданная как дань классической серии Bomberman. Она сочетает динамичный стратегический геймплей с улучшениями, такими как новые механики, большое разнообразие персонажей и широкие возможности настройки, сохраняя оригинальное очарование взрывов и соперничества.

• Динамичный геймплей для игры до 12 человек
• Боевой режим включает Быстрый бой, Локальный бой и Онлайн-бой
• 6 различных правил боевого режима: Survival Battle, Reversi Battle, Dodge Battle, Hyper Bomber, King Battle, Battle Royale
• Режим очков — ремейк Bomberman для NES, также включающий усиленный Turbo-режим
• Огромное количество различных предметов: многие из них хорошо знакомы, а некоторые вы увидите впервые
• Более 700 разблокируемых игровых персонажей со всей истории серии, а также несколько гостей от Konami
• Более 80 уровней, всего около 700 игровых вариантов
• Множество настроек — от Revenge Bomber и Sudden Death из оригинальных игр до более детальных параметров, таких как длина фитиля бомбы, тайминг взрыва или урон от Pressure Blocks
• и многое другое!</text>
			<text lang="pl">Power Bomberman to gra stworzona przez fanów jako hołd dla klasycznej serii Bomberman. Łączy dynamiczną, strategiczną rozgrywkę z ulepszeniami, takimi jak nowe mechaniki, duża różnorodność postaci oraz rozbudowane opcje personalizacji, zachowując oryginalny urok eksplozji i rywalizacji.

- Dynamiczna rozgrywka dla maksymalnie 12 graczy
- Tryb Bitwy obejmuje Szybką Bitwę, Bitwę Lokalną oraz Bitwę Online
- 6 różnych zasad trybu Bitwy: Survival Battle, Reversi Battle, Dodge Battle, Hyper Bomber, King Battle, Battle Royale
- Tryb Punktowy — remake Bombermana z NES-a, zawierający również wzmocniony tryb Turbo
- Mnóstwo różnorodnych przedmiotów, z których wiele jest już dobrze znanych, a część zupełnie nowych
- Ponad 700 odblokowywanych grywalnych postaci z całej historii serii, w tym kilku gości od Konami
- Ponad 80 plansz, łącznie około 700 wariantów do gry
- Wiele ustawień, od klasycznych Revenge Bomber i Sudden Death po bardziej zaawansowane opcje, takie jak długość lontu bomby, czas eksplozji czy obrażenia zadawane przez bloki nacisku
- i wiele więcej!</text>
			<text lang="pt">Power Bomberman é um jogo feito por fãs, criado como uma homenagem à clássica série Bomberman. Ele combina jogabilidade estratégica e frenética com melhorias como novas mecânicas, uma grande variedade de personagens e amplas opções de personalização, preservando o charme original das explosões e da rivalidade.

• Jogabilidade frenética para até 12 jogadores
• O modo Batalha inclui Batalha Rápida, Batalha Local e Batalha Online
• 6 regras diferentes do modo Batalha: Survival Battle, Reversi Battle, Dodge Battle, Hyper Bomber, King Battle, Battle Royale
• Modo Pontuação — um remake do Bomberman de NES, incluindo também um modo Turbo aprimorado
• Uma grande variedade de itens, muitos já conhecidos e adorados, e outros nunca vistos antes
• Mais de 700 personagens jogáveis desbloqueáveis de toda a história da série, juntamente com alguns convidados da Konami
• Mais de 80 fases, totalizando cerca de 700 variantes jogáveis
• Muitas configurações diferentes, desde Revenge Bomber e Sudden Death dos jogos originais até opções mais avançadas como o tempo do pavio da bomba, o tempo da explosão ou o dano causado pelos blocos de pressão
• e muito mais!</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>