<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.5 0.4894</pos>
			<size>0.308 0.25</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.34 0.25</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.41 0.25</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.23 0.25</size>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<pos>0.5 0.491</pos>
			<maxSize>0.25</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.27</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.328</maxSize>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>2006</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>Sony</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>PlayStation Network</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextVariant">
			<text>PS3</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>PlayStation Network (PSN) is a digital multimedia content distribution and online gaming service provided by Sony Interactive Entertainment for use with PlayStation 3, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, PlayStation Portable, and PlayStation Vita consoles. It enables downloading digital content and playing online multiplayer games (on PS4, access to online multiplayer requires a paid PlayStation Plus subscription). In 2011, PSN suffered a major security breach that potentially affected 77 million user accounts, leading to a service shutdown that lasted about a month.

As of July 2013, PlayStation Network had more than 110 million registered users worldwide. On September 15, 2014, PSN discontinued support for the PlayStation Portable.

In February 2025, Sony reported that PSN had 129 million monthly active users.

In August 2025, during an investor meeting, Sony Senior Vice President Sadahiko Hayakawa stated that “PlayStation is shifting from a hardware-focused business to one centered on community engagement.”</text>
			<text lang="pl">PlayStation Network (PSN) to usługa dystrybucji cyfrowych treści multimedialnych oraz rozgrywki sieciowej oferowana przez Sony Interactive Entertainment dla konsol PlayStation 3, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, PlayStation Portable oraz PlayStation Vita. Umożliwia pobieranie treści cyfrowych oraz grę w trybie wieloosobowym online (na PS4 dostęp do gry online wymaga płatnej subskrypcji PlayStation Plus). W 2011 roku doszło do poważnego włamania do sieci PSN, które mogło dotknąć 77 milionów kont użytkowników, co doprowadziło do wyłączenia usługi na około miesiąc.

Według stanu na lipiec 2013 roku PSN liczył ponad 110 milionów zarejestrowanych użytkowników na całym świecie. Od 15 września 2014 roku usługa PSN zakończyła obsługę PlayStation Portable.

W lutym 2025 roku Sony poinformowało, że PSN ma 129 milionów aktywnych użytkowników miesięcznie.

W sierpniu 2025 roku, podczas spotkania z inwestorami, starszy wiceprezes Sony Sadahiko Hayakawa stwierdził, że „PlayStation przechodzi od modelu biznesowego opartego na sprzęcie do modelu skoncentrowanego na społeczności”.</text>
			<text lang="ru">PlayStation Network (PSN) — сервис загрузки цифрового мультимедийного контента и проведения бесплатных (на PS4 для получения доступа к сетевой игре требуется наличие платной подписки PlayStation Plus) сетевых многопользовательских игр, предоставляемый компанией Sony Interactive Entertainment для использования с игровыми приставками PlayStation 3, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, PlayStation Portable и PlayStation Vita. В 2011 году произошёл крупнейший взлом сети PSN, потенциально затронувший 77 млн учётных записей сервиса, за которым последовало отключение и неработоспособность сервиса в течение месяца.

По состоянию на июль 2013 года PlayStation Network насчитывает более 110 миллионов зарегистрированных пользователей по всему миру. С 15 сентября 2014 года сервис PSN прекратил обслуживание PlayStation Portable.

В феврале 2025 года Sony заявила, что ежемесячная аудитория PSN составляет 129 миллионов активных пользователей.

В августе 2025 года, в рамках встречи с инвесторами, старший вице-президент Sony Садахико Хаякава заявил, что «PlayStation переходит от бизнеса, ориентированного на аппаратное обеспечение, к бизнесу, ориентированному на взаимодействие с сообществом».</text>
			<text lang="es">PlayStation Network (PSN) es un servicio de distribución de contenido multimedia digital y juego en línea proporcionado por Sony Interactive Entertainment para las consolas PlayStation 3, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, PlayStation Portable y PlayStation Vita. Permite descargar contenido digital y jugar en modo multijugador online (en PS4, el acceso al juego en línea requiere una suscripción de pago a PlayStation Plus). En 2011, PSN sufrió un importante ataque de seguridad que pudo afectar a 77 millones de cuentas, lo que provocó la interrupción del servicio durante aproximadamente un mes.

En julio de 2013, PlayStation Network contaba con más de 110 millones de usuarios registrados en todo el mundo. Desde el 15 de septiembre de 2014, el servicio dejó de dar soporte a PlayStation Portable.

En febrero de 2025, Sony informó que PSN cuenta con 129 millones de usuarios activos mensuales.

En agosto de 2025, durante una reunión con inversores, el vicepresidente senior de Sony, Sadahiko Hayakawa, declaró que «PlayStation está pasando de un negocio centrado en el hardware a uno centrado en la comunidad».</text>
			<text lang="de">PlayStation Network (PSN) ist ein Dienst zur Verteilung digitaler Multimedia-Inhalte und für Online-Spiele, der von Sony Interactive Entertainment für die Konsolen PlayStation 3, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, PlayStation Portable und PlayStation Vita bereitgestellt wird. Er ermöglicht das Herunterladen digitaler Inhalte sowie das Spielen von Online-Multiplayer-Spielen (auf der PS4 ist hierfür ein kostenpflichtiges PlayStation-Plus-Abonnement erforderlich). Im Jahr 2011 kam es zu einem großen Sicherheitsvorfall, bei dem möglicherweise 77 Millionen Benutzerkonten betroffen waren, was zu einem etwa einmonatigen Ausfall des Dienstes führte.

Im Juli 2013 hatte das PlayStation Network weltweit über 110 Millionen registrierte Nutzer. Seit dem 15. September 2014 unterstützt der Dienst die PlayStation Portable nicht mehr.

Im Februar 2025 gab Sony bekannt, dass PSN monatlich 129 Millionen aktive Nutzer hat.

Im August 2025 erklärte Sonys Senior Vice President Sadahiko Hayakawa auf einer Investorenkonferenz, dass „PlayStation sich von einem hardwarezentrierten Geschäft hin zu einem auf Community-Interaktion ausgerichteten Modell entwickelt“.</text>
			<text lang="fr">PlayStation Network (PSN) est un service de distribution de contenu multimédia numérique et de jeu en ligne proposé par Sony Interactive Entertainment pour les consoles PlayStation 3, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, PlayStation Portable et PlayStation Vita. Il permet de télécharger du contenu numérique et de jouer en multijoueur en ligne (sur PS4, l’accès au jeu en ligne nécessite un abonnement payant PlayStation Plus). En 2011, PSN a subi une importante faille de sécurité qui a potentiellement affecté 77 millions de comptes, entraînant une interruption du service pendant environ un mois.

En juillet 2013, PlayStation Network comptait plus de 110 millions d’utilisateurs enregistrés dans le monde. Depuis le 15 septembre 2014, le service ne prend plus en charge la PlayStation Portable.

En février 2025, Sony a annoncé que PSN compte 129 millions d’utilisateurs actifs mensuels.

En août 2025, lors d’une réunion avec les investisseurs, le vice-président senior de Sony, Sadahiko Hayakawa, a déclaré que « PlayStation évolue d’un modèle centré sur le matériel vers un modèle axé sur la communauté ».</text>
			<text lang="it">PlayStation Network (PSN) è un servizio di distribuzione di contenuti multimediali digitali e gioco online fornito da Sony Interactive Entertainment per le console PlayStation 3, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, PlayStation Portable e PlayStation Vita. Consente di scaricare contenuti digitali e giocare in modalità multiplayer online (su PS4 l’accesso al gioco online richiede un abbonamento a pagamento PlayStation Plus). Nel 2011 PSN ha subito una grave violazione della sicurezza che ha potenzialmente coinvolto 77 milioni di account, causando un’interruzione del servizio di circa un mese.

A luglio 2013, PlayStation Network contava oltre 110 milioni di utenti registrati in tutto il mondo. Dal 15 settembre 2014 il servizio ha cessato il supporto per PlayStation Portable.

Nel febbraio 2025, Sony ha dichiarato che PSN ha 129 milioni di utenti attivi mensili.

Nell’agosto 2025, durante un incontro con gli investitori, il vicepresidente senior di Sony Sadahiko Hayakawa ha affermato che «PlayStation sta passando da un modello di business incentrato sull’hardware a uno basato sull’interazione con la comunità».</text>
			<text lang="pt">A PlayStation Network (PSN) é um serviço de distribuição de conteúdo multimédia digital e jogos online fornecido pela Sony Interactive Entertainment para as consolas PlayStation 3, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, PlayStation Portable e PlayStation Vita. Permite o download de conteúdos digitais e o jogo multijogador online (na PS4, o acesso ao jogo online requer uma subscrição paga PlayStation Plus). Em 2011, a PSN sofreu uma grande violação de segurança que afetou potencialmente 77 milhões de contas, levando a uma interrupção do serviço durante cerca de um mês.

Em julho de 2013, a PlayStation Network contava com mais de 110 milhões de utilizadores registados em todo o mundo. Desde 15 de setembro de 2014, o serviço deixou de suportar a PlayStation Portable.

Em fevereiro de 2025, a Sony afirmou que a PSN tem 129 milhões de utilizadores ativos mensais.

Em agosto de 2025, durante uma reunião com investidores, o vice-presidente sénior da Sony, Sadahiko Hayakawa, declarou que «a PlayStation está a passar de um modelo de negócio centrado no hardware para um focado na interação com a comunidade».</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
