<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<visible>false</visible>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<visible>false</visible>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>2020</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>OpenDriver2</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>ReDriver 2</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextVariant">
			<text>Port</text>
			<text lang="pl">Port</text>
			<text lang="ru">Порт</text>
			<text lang="es">Puerto</text>
			<text lang="de">Hafen</text>
			<text lang="fr">Port</text>
			<text lang="it">Port</text>
			<text lang="pt">Porto</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>The fan-made port of the legendary Driver 2 from the original PlayStation, titled ReDriver 2, is distributed completely free of charge. The developers not only brought the original game to PC, but also improved the graphics, draw distance, added widescreen support, and much more.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Fanowski port legendarnego Driver 2 z pierwszego PlayStation, zatytułowany ReDriver 2, jest udostępniany całkowicie za darmo. Twórcy nie tylko przenieśli oryginalną grę na PC, ale także poprawili grafikę, zasięg rysowania, dodali tryb szerokoekranowy i wiele więcej.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Фанатский порт легендарной Driver 2 с первой PlayStation под названием ReDriver 2, распространяется абсолютно бесплатно. Разработчики не только перенесли оригинальную игру на ПК, но и улучшили графику, дальность прорисовки, добавили широкоформатный режим и много чего ещё.</text>
			<text lang="es">El port fan del legendario Driver 2 de la primera PlayStation, titulado ReDriver 2, se distribuye completamente gratis. Los desarrolladores no solo trasladaron el juego original a PC, sino que también mejoraron los gráficos, la distancia de dibujado, añadieron soporte para pantalla panorámica y mucho más.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Fan-Port des legendären Driver 2 von der ersten PlayStation mit dem Titel ReDriver 2 wird völlig kostenlos verbreitet. Die Entwickler haben das Originalspiel nicht nur auf den PC gebracht, sondern auch die Grafik, die Sichtweite verbessert, einen Breitbildmodus hinzugefügt und vieles mehr.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le port réalisé par des fans du légendaire Driver 2 de la première PlayStation, intitulé ReDriver 2, est distribué entièrement gratuitement. Les développeurs ont non seulement porté le jeu original sur PC, mais ont aussi amélioré les graphismes, la distance d’affichage, ajouté le mode écran large et bien plus encore.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il port fan-made del leggendario Driver 2 della prima PlayStation, intitolato ReDriver 2, è distribuito completamente бесплатно. Gli sviluppatori non solo hanno portato il gioco originale su PC, ma hanno anche migliorato la grafica, la distanza di visualizzazione, aggiunto il supporto widescreen e molto altro.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O port feito por fãs do lendário Driver 2 do primeiro PlayStation, intitulado ReDriver 2, é distribuído totalmente de graça. Os desenvolvedores não apenas levaram o jogo original para PC, mas também melhoraram os gráficos, a distância de renderização, adicionaram suporte a widescreen e muito mais.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
