<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<visible>false</visible>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<visible>false</visible>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>1995</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>Tiger</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>R-Zone</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>The R-Zone is a portable game console (originally head-worn, later handheld) developed and manufactured by Tiger Electronics. The R-Zone was shown at the American International Toy Fair in February 1995, and was released later that year. The R-Zone was panned by critics, and was also a commercial disaster, with its lifespan lasting only two years before being discontinued in 1997. Although the R-Zone was not designed to compete directly with any other handhelds, it marked Tiger Electronics' first multi-game entry into the portable electronic game market.

The original R-Zone unit consists of a headset and a separate controller containing batteries. Each game cartridge has its own transparent LCD screen which is projected onto a mirrored surface held in front of the player's eye. It is thought that this original design, including the red color scheme, was designed to capitalize on popular buzz for the Nintendo Virtual Boy at the time. However, Tiger has never confirmed this theory.

Three additional versions of the R-Zone were subsequently released: the R-Zone SuperScreen, the XPG (Xtreme Pocket Game), and the DataZone. It has been constantly regarded as one of the worst video game consoles ever made.</text>
			<text lang="pl">R-Zone to przenośna konsola do gier (początkowo montowana na głowie, później w formie handhelda) opracowana i produkowana przez Tiger Electronics. Została zaprezentowana na targach American International Toy Fair w lutym 1995 roku, a na rynek trafiła później w tym samym roku. R-Zone spotkała się z bardzo negatywnymi opiniami i okazała się komercyjną porażką — jej cykl życia wyniósł zaledwie dwa lata, zanim została wycofana w 1997 roku. Choć nie była bezpośrednio projektowana jako konkurencja dla innych konsol przenośnych, stanowiła pierwszą wielogrową platformę Tiger Electronics na rynku gier przenośnych.

Pierwsza wersja R-Zone składała się z zestawu słuchawkowego oraz oddzielnego kontrolera zawierającego baterie. Każdy kartridż posiadał własny przezroczysty ekran LCD, którego obraz był wyświetlany na lustrzanej powierzchni umieszczonej przed okiem gracza. Uważa się, że taka konstrukcja, w tym czerwona kolorystyka, miała wykorzystać popularność konsoli Nintendo Virtual Boy, choć firma Tiger nigdy oficjalnie tego nie potwierdziła.

Później wydano trzy dodatkowe wersje: R-Zone SuperScreen, XPG (Xtreme Pocket Game) oraz DataZone. System ten jest powszechnie uznawany za jedną z najgorszych konsol do gier w historii.</text>
			<text lang="ru">R-Zone — это портативная игровая консоль (изначально носимая на голове, позднее — в виде карманного устройства), разработанная и выпущенная компанией Tiger Electronics. Она была представлена на выставке American International Toy Fair в феврале 1995 года и поступила в продажу позже в том же году. R-Zone получила крайне негативные отзывы и стала коммерческим провалом, просуществовав всего два года и будучи снятой с производства в 1997 году. Хотя она не создавалась как прямой конкурент другим портативным системам, это была первая многокартриджная игровая платформа Tiger Electronics на рынке портативных игр.

Оригинальная версия R-Zone состояла из гарнитуры и отдельного контроллера с батареями. Каждый игровой картридж имел собственный прозрачный ЖК-экран, изображение с которого проецировалось на зеркальную поверхность перед глазом игрока. Считается, что такой дизайн, включая красную цветовую схему, был вдохновлён популярностью Nintendo Virtual Boy, однако компания Tiger никогда официально этого не подтверждала.

Позднее были выпущены ещё три версии: R-Zone SuperScreen, XPG (Xtreme Pocket Game) и DataZone. Консоль часто считается одной из худших игровых систем в истории.</text>
			<text lang="es">R-Zone es una consola portátil (originalmente para llevar en la cabeza, posteriormente tipo handheld) desarrollada y fabricada por Tiger Electronics. Fue presentada en la American International Toy Fair en febrero de 1995 y lanzada más tarde ese mismo año. La R-Zone recibió críticas muy negativas y fue un fracaso comercial, con una vida útil de solo dos años antes de ser descontinuada en 1997. Aunque no fue diseñada para competir directamente con otras consolas portátiles, marcó la primera incursión de Tiger Electronics en el mercado de sistemas portátiles con múltiples juegos.

La unidad original de R-Zone consta de un visor y un controlador separado que contiene las baterías. Cada cartucho de juego incluye su propia pantalla LCD transparente, cuya imagen se proyecta sobre una superficie reflectante frente al ojo del jugador. Se cree que este diseño, incluido el esquema de color rojo, pretendía aprovechar la popularidad de la Nintendo Virtual Boy, aunque Tiger nunca lo ha confirmado oficialmente.

Posteriormente se lanzaron tres versiones adicionales: R-Zone SuperScreen, XPG (Xtreme Pocket Game) y DataZone. El sistema es ampliamente considerado como una de las peores consolas de videojuegos jamás creadas.</text>
			<text lang="de">Die R-Zone ist eine tragbare Spielkonsole (ursprünglich als Headset getragen, später als Handheld), die von Tiger Electronics entwickelt und hergestellt wurde. Sie wurde im Februar 1995 auf der American International Toy Fair vorgestellt und noch im selben Jahr veröffentlicht. Die R-Zone wurde von Kritikern verrissen und war ein kommerzieller Misserfolg; ihre Lebensdauer betrug nur zwei Jahre, bevor sie 1997 eingestellt wurde. Obwohl sie nicht als direkter Konkurrent zu anderen Handhelds gedacht war, stellte sie den ersten Mehrspiel-Einstieg von Tiger Electronics in den Markt für tragbare Spiele dar.

Die ursprüngliche R-Zone bestand aus einem Headset und einem separaten Controller mit Batterien. Jedes Spielmodul verfügte über ein eigenes transparentes LCD-Display, dessen Bild auf eine reflektierende Fläche vor dem Auge des Spielers projiziert wurde. Es wird angenommen, dass dieses Design, einschließlich der roten Farbgebung, von der Popularität des Nintendo Virtual Boy profitieren sollte, obwohl Tiger dies nie offiziell bestätigt hat.

Später erschienen drei weitere Versionen: R-Zone SuperScreen, XPG (Xtreme Pocket Game) und DataZone. Das System gilt weithin als eine der schlechtesten Videospielkonsolen aller Zeiten.</text>
			<text lang="fr">La R-Zone est une console de jeu portable (initialement portée sur la tête, puis sous forme de console portable classique) développée et fabriquée par Tiger Electronics. Elle a été présentée lors de l’American International Toy Fair en février 1995 et commercialisée plus tard la même année. La R-Zone a été très mal accueillie par la critique et a été un échec commercial, avec une durée de vie de seulement deux ans avant son arrêt en 1997. Bien qu’elle n’ait pas été conçue pour concurrencer directement les autres consoles portables, elle représentait la première plateforme multi-jeux de Tiger Electronics sur le marché du jeu portable.

Le modèle original de la R-Zone se compose d’un casque et d’un contrôleur séparé contenant les piles. Chaque cartouche de jeu possède son propre écran LCD transparent, dont l’image est projetée sur une surface réfléchissante placée devant l’œil du joueur. On pense que ce design, y compris la couleur rouge, visait à tirer parti de la popularité du Nintendo Virtual Boy, bien que cela n’ait jamais été confirmé officiellement par Tiger.

Trois autres versions ont ensuite été commercialisées : la R-Zone SuperScreen, la XPG (Xtreme Pocket Game) et la DataZone. La console est largement considérée comme l’une des pires jamais produites.</text>
			<text lang="it">R-Zone è una console portatile (inizialmente indossabile sulla testa, successivamente in formato handheld) sviluppata e prodotta da Tiger Electronics. È stata presentata all’American International Toy Fair nel febbraio 1995 e lanciata sul mercato più tardi nello stesso anno. La R-Zone è stata duramente criticata ed è stata un fallimento commerciale, con una durata di vita di soli due anni prima di essere ritirata nel 1997. Sebbene non fosse progettata per competere direttamente con altre console portatili, rappresentò il primo sistema multi-gioco di Tiger Electronics nel mercato del gaming portatile.

L’unità originale R-Zone consiste in un visore e un controller separato contenente le batterie. Ogni cartuccia di gioco dispone di un proprio schermo LCD trasparente, la cui immagine viene proiettata su una superficie riflettente davanti all’occhio del giocatore. Si ritiene che questo design, inclusa la colorazione rossa, fosse pensato per sfruttare la popolarità del Nintendo Virtual Boy, anche se Tiger non lo ha mai confermato ufficialmente.

Successivamente sono state rilasciate tre versioni aggiuntive: R-Zone SuperScreen, XPG (Xtreme Pocket Game) e DataZone. Il sistema è spesso considerato una delle peggiori console mai realizzate.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O R-Zone é um console portátil (inicialmente usado na cabeça, posteriormente no formato handheld) desenvolvido e fabricado pela Tiger Electronics. Foi apresentado na American International Toy Fair em fevereiro de 1995 e lançado no mercado ainda nesse ano. O R-Zone recebeu críticas extremamente negativas e foi um fracasso comercial, com uma vida útil de apenas dois anos antes de ser descontinuado em 1997. Embora não tenha sido projetado para competir diretamente com outros consoles portáteis, marcou a primeira entrada multi-jogo da Tiger Electronics no mercado de jogos portáteis.

A unidade original do R-Zone consiste num visor e num controlador separado que contém as baterias. Cada cartucho de jogo possui o seu próprio ecrã LCD transparente, cuja imagem é projetada numa superfície refletora colocada diante do olho do jogador. Acredita-se que este design, incluindo a cor vermelha, tenha sido pensado para aproveitar a popularidade do Nintendo Virtual Boy, embora a Tiger nunca tenha confirmado oficialmente essa teoria.

Posteriormente foram lançadas três versões adicionais: R-Zone SuperScreen, XPG (Xtreme Pocket Game) e DataZone. O sistema é amplamente considerado um dos piores consoles de videojogos já criados.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
