<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-left">
			<pos>0.305 0.45</pos>
			<size>0.1 0.3</size>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.95 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.64 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.14 0.5</origin>
			<visible>true</visible>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-right">
			<pos>0.695 0.45</pos>
			<size>0.1 0.3</size>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.04 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.36 0.5</origin>
			<origin if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.86 0.5</origin>
			<visible>true</visible>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.499 0.47</pos>
			<size>0.32 0.22</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.36 0.22</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.42 0.22</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.27 0.22</size>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<pos>0.4994 0.47</pos>
			<maxSize>0.3</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.34</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.41</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.23</maxSize>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>2013</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>Sega</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>Nu</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>The Nu is an arcade board created by Sega. The board superseded the Ring family of systems with slightly more advanced PC-based hardware, though releases for both still appeared into the late 2010s. It debuted with Hatsune Miku: Project DIVA Arcade Future Tone, released in Japan, Asia, and in a limited exclusive capacity in across the US through Round1 locations.

The original Nu hardware was only selected for one other game series in Japan, Wonderland Wars, before being replaced by its modified successors Nu 1.1, Nu 2, and the lower-cost Nu SX. These collectively received slightly more releases both in Japan and internationally (the latter generally for overseas-friendly titles based on the Mario and Sonic properties).</text>
			<text lang="it">Nu è una scheda arcade creata da Sega. La scheda ha sostituito la famiglia di sistemi Ring con hardware basato su PC leggermente più avanzato, sebbene le uscite per entrambe le piattaforme siano continuate fino alla fine degli anni 2010. Ha debuttato con Hatsune Miku: Project DIVA Arcade Future Tone, pubblicato in Giappone, in Asia e, in forma limitata ed esclusiva, negli Stati Uniti tramite le sale Round1.

L’hardware Nu originale fu scelto in Giappone solo per un’altra serie di giochi, Wonderland Wars, prima di essere sostituito dai successori modificati Nu 1.1, Nu 2 e dal modello a basso costo Nu SX. Questi sistemi nel loro complesso ricevettero un numero leggermente maggiore di titoli sia in Giappone sia a livello internazionale (quest’ultimi generalmente per giochi più adatti al pubblico estero basati sulle proprietà di Mario e Sonic).</text>
			<text lang="fr">Nu est une carte arcade créée par Sega. Elle a succédé à la famille de systèmes Ring avec un matériel basé sur PC légèrement plus avancé, bien que des sorties pour les deux plateformes aient continué jusqu’à la fin des années 2010. Elle a fait ses débuts avec Hatsune Miku: Project DIVA Arcade Future Tone, sorti au Japon, en Asie et, de manière limitée et exclusive, aux États-Unis via les salles Round1.

Le matériel Nu original n’a été choisi au Japon que pour une seule autre série de jeux, Wonderland Wars, avant d’être remplacé par ses successeurs modifiés Nu 1.1, Nu 2 et le modèle à moindre coût Nu SX. L’ensemble de ces systèmes a bénéficié d’un nombre légèrement supérieur de sorties, tant au Japon qu’à l’international (ces dernières étant généralement des titres plus accessibles au public étranger basés sur les licences Mario et Sonic).</text>
			<text lang="de">Nu ist ein von Sega entwickeltes Arcade-Board. Es löste die Ring-Systemfamilie mit etwas fortschrittlicherer, PC-basierter Hardware ab, wobei Veröffentlichungen für beide Plattformen noch bis in die späten 2010er Jahre erschienen. Sein Debüt feierte es mit Hatsune Miku: Project DIVA Arcade Future Tone, das in Japan, Asien sowie in begrenztem, exklusivem Umfang auch in den USA über Round1-Spielhallen veröffentlicht wurde.

Die ursprüngliche Nu-Hardware wurde in Japan nur für eine weitere Spielereihe, Wonderland Wars, eingesetzt, bevor sie durch die modifizierten Nachfolger Nu 1.1, Nu 2 und das kostengünstigere Nu SX ersetzt wurde. Diese Systeme erhielten zusammen etwas mehr Veröffentlichungen sowohl in Japan als auch international (letztere meist für auslandsfreundliche Titel auf Basis der Marken Mario und Sonic).</text>
			<text lang="es">Nu es una placa arcade creada por Sega. Sustituyó a la familia de sistemas Ring con un hardware basado en PC ligeramente más avanzado, aunque los lanzamientos para ambos continuaron hasta finales de la década de 2010. Debutó con Hatsune Miku: Project DIVA Arcade Future Tone, lanzado en Japón, Asia y, de forma limitada y exclusiva, en Estados Unidos a través de las salas Round1.

El hardware Nu original solo fue elegido en Japón para otra serie de juegos, Wonderland Wars, antes de ser reemplazado por sus sucesores modificados Nu 1.1, Nu 2 y el modelo de menor costo Nu SX. En conjunto, estos sistemas recibieron un número ligeramente mayor de lanzamientos tanto en Japón como a nivel internacional (estos últimos, por lo general, títulos más accesibles para el público extranjero basados en las franquicias de Mario y Sonic).</text>
			<text lang="ru">Nu — это аркадная плата, созданная компанией Sega. Она пришла на смену семейству систем Ring, предложив немного более продвинутое аппаратное обеспечение на базе ПК, хотя релизы для обеих платформ продолжали выходить вплоть до конца 2010-х годов. Дебют состоялся с игрой Hatsune Miku: Project DIVA Arcade Future Tone, выпущенной в Японии, Азии, а также в ограниченном эксклюзивном формате в США через залы Round1.

Оригинальное аппаратное обеспечение Nu в Японии было выбрано лишь для одной другой серии игр — Wonderland Wars, после чего его заменили модифицированные преемники Nu 1.1, Nu 2 и более доступная по цене версия Nu SX. В совокупности эти системы получили немного больше релизов как в Японии, так и за её пределами (последние, как правило, представляли собой более ориентированные на зарубежный рынок проекты на основе франшиз Mario и Sonic).</text>
			<text lang="pl">Nu to płyta arcade stworzona przez firmę Sega. Zastąpiła ona rodzinę systemów Ring, oferując nieco bardziej zaawansowany sprzęt oparty na PC, choć wydania na obie platformy pojawiały się jeszcze do końca lat 2010. Zadebiutowała wraz z grą Hatsune Miku: Project DIVA Arcade Future Tone, wydaną w Japonii, Azji oraz w ograniczonym, ekskluzywnym zakresie w Stanach Zjednoczonych za pośrednictwem salonów Round1.

Oryginalny sprzęt Nu został w Japonii wybrany tylko dla jednej dodatkowej serii gier, Wonderland Wars, zanim został zastąpiony przez zmodyfikowanych następców Nu 1.1, Nu 2 oraz tańszy model Nu SX. Łącznie systemy te doczekały się nieco większej liczby wydań zarówno w Japonii, jak i na rynkach międzynarodowych (te ostatnie zazwyczaj obejmowały tytuły bardziej przyjazne dla zagranicznych odbiorców, oparte na markach Mario i Sonic).</text>
			<text lang="pt">Nu é uma placa arcade criada pela Sega. Ela substituiu a família de sistemas Ring com um hardware baseado em PC ligeiramente mais avançado, embora lançamentos para ambos ainda tenham ocorrido até o final da década de 2010. Ela estreou com Hatsune Miku: Project DIVA Arcade Future Tone, lançado no Japão, na Ásia e, de forma limitada e exclusiva, nos Estados Unidos por meio das casas Round1.

O hardware Nu original foi selecionado no Japão apenas para outra série de jogos, Wonderland Wars, antes de ser substituído por seus sucessores modificados Nu 1.1, Nu 2 e pelo modelo de menor custo Nu SX. Em conjunto, esses sistemas receberam um número um pouco maior de lançamentos tanto no Japão quanto internacionalmente (estes últimos geralmente para títulos mais acessíveis ao público estrangeiro baseados nas propriedades Mario e Sonic).</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
