<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.499 0.39</pos>
			<size>0.2 0.25</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.22 0.25</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.27 0.25</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.15 0.25</size>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<pos>0.499 0.39</pos>
			<maxSize>0.242</maxSize>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>1994</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>Sega / TCI / Time Warner Cable</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>Sega Channel</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>Sega Channel was an online game service developed by Sega for the Sega Genesis video game console, functioning as a content delivery system. Launched on December 12, 1994, Sega Channel was provided to users by TCI and Time Warner Cable through cable television services via coaxial cable. It was a paid service that allowed users to access Genesis games online, play demos, and use cheat codes.

The service operated until July 31, 1998—continuing for three years after the release of Sega’s next-generation console, the Sega Saturn. Despite criticism for its poorly timed launch and high subscription cost, Sega Channel received recognition for its innovations in downloadable content and its influence on the development of online gaming services.

Of particular interest to enthusiasts is a collection that also includes dozens of previously unreleased game variants and Sega Channel exclusives. This compilation features Garfield: Caught in the Act – The Lost Levels and The Flintstones, two games that were previously considered permanently lost and unrecoverable.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Sega Channel był usługą gier online opracowaną przez firmę Sega dla konsoli Sega Genesis, pełniącą funkcję systemu dystrybucji treści. Uruchomiony 12 grudnia 1994 roku, Sega Channel był udostępniany użytkownikom przez TCI i Time Warner Cable za pośrednictwem telewizji kablowej przy użyciu kabla koncentrycznego. Była to usługa płatna, umożliwiająca dostęp do gier na Genesis online, granie w dema oraz korzystanie z kodów do gier.

Usługa działała do 31 lipca 1998 roku — jeszcze przez trzy lata po premierze konsoli nowej generacji Sega, czyli Sega Saturn. Pomimo krytyki za nieodpowiedni moment premiery i wysoką cenę abonamentu, Sega Channel zdobył uznanie za innowacje w zakresie treści do pobrania oraz wpływ na rozwój usług gier online.

Szczególne zainteresowanie wśród fanów budzi kolekcja, która zawiera także dziesiątki wcześniej niepublikowanych wersji gier oraz ekskluzywów Sega Channel. W skład tej kompilacji wchodzą Garfield: Caught in the Act – The Lost Levels oraz The Flintstones — dwie gry, które wcześniej uznawano za bezpowrotnie utracone i niemożliwe do odzyskania.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Sega Channel — это онлайн-сервис распространения игр, разработанный компанией Sega для игровой консоли Sega Genesis. Фактически Sega экспериментировала с концепцией цифрового игрового сервиса задолго до появления современных онлайн-магазинов и стриминговых платформ. Запущенный 12 декабря 1994 года, Sega Channel предоставлялся пользователям компаниями TCI и Time Warner Cable через сети кабельного телевидения по коаксиальному кабелю. Это был платный сервис, который позволял пользователям получать доступ к играм для Genesis, запускать демоверсии, заранее записанный игровой процесс и использовать чит-коды.

Сервис работал до 31 июля 1998 года — ещё три года после выхода консоли нового поколения Sega Saturn. Несмотря на критику из-за неудачно выбранного времени запуска и высокой стоимости подписки, Sega Channel получил признание за свои новаторские решения в области загружаемого контента и влияние на дальнейшее развитие сервисов для онлайн-игр.

Коллекция включает в себя десятки ранее не публиковавшихся вариантов игр и эксклюзивов Sega Channel. В эту подборку входят Garfield: Caught in the Act – The Lost Levels и The Flintstones, две игры, которые ранее считались безвозвратно утерянными и не подлежащими восстановлению.</text>
			<text lang="es">Sega Channel fue un servicio de juegos en línea desarrollado por Sega para la consola Sega Genesis, que funcionaba como un sistema de distribución de contenido. Lanzado el 12 de diciembre de 1994, Sega Channel fue ofrecido a los usuarios por TCI y Time Warner Cable a través de servicios de televisión por cable mediante cable coaxial. Era un servicio de pago que permitía acceder a juegos de Genesis en línea, jugar demos y utilizar trucos.

El servicio estuvo activo hasta el 31 de julio de 1998, continuando durante tres años después del lanzamiento de la consola de nueva generación de Sega, la Sega Saturn. A pesar de las críticas por su lanzamiento en un momento poco adecuado y por el alto costo de suscripción, Sega Channel fue reconocido por sus innovaciones en contenido descargable y su influencia en el desarrollo de los servicios de juegos en línea.

De especial interés para los aficionados es una colección que también incluye decenas de versiones de juegos previamente inéditas y exclusivas de Sega Channel. Esta recopilación incluye Garfield: Caught in the Act – The Lost Levels y The Flintstones, dos juegos que anteriormente se consideraban perdidos de forma irrecuperable.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der Sega Channel war ein Online-Spieledienst von Sega für die Videospielkonsole Sega Genesis und diente als Content-Distributionssystem. Er wurde am 12. Dezember 1994 gestartet und von TCI und Time Warner Cable über Kabel-TV-Dienste mittels Koaxialkabel bereitgestellt. Es handelte sich um einen kostenpflichtigen Dienst, über den Nutzer online auf Genesis-Spiele zugreifen, Demos spielen und Cheat-Codes nutzen konnten.

Der Dienst lief bis zum 31. Juli 1998 und war damit noch drei Jahre nach der Veröffentlichung von Segas Next-Gen-Konsole, der Sega Saturn, aktiv. Trotz Kritik an seinem ungünstigen Veröffentlichungszeitpunkt und den hohen Abonnementkosten wurde der Sega Channel für seine Innovationen im Bereich herunterladbarer Inhalte und seinen Einfluss auf Online-Gaming-Dienste anerkannt.

Von besonderem Interesse für Fans ist eine Sammlung, die auch Dutzende zuvor unveröffentlichter Spielversionen und exklusiver Sega-Channel-Titel umfasst. Dazu gehören Garfield: Caught in the Act – The Lost Levels und The Flintstones, zwei Spiele, die zuvor als unwiederbringlich verloren galten.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le Sega Channel était un service de jeux en ligne développé par Sega pour la console Sega Genesis, servant de système de distribution de contenu. Lancé le 12 décembre 1994, il était proposé aux utilisateurs par TCI et Time Warner Cable via les services de télévision par câble à l’aide d’un câble coaxial. Il s’agissait d’un service payant permettant d’accéder à des jeux Genesis en ligne, de jouer à des démos et d’utiliser des codes de triche.

Le service a fonctionné jusqu’au 31 juillet 1998, soit encore trois ans après la sortie de la console nouvelle génération de Sega, la Sega Saturn. Malgré des critiques concernant le moment de son lancement et le coût élevé de l’abonnement, le Sega Channel a été reconnu pour ses innovations en matière de contenu téléchargeable et son influence sur les services de jeux en ligne.

Un intérêt particulier pour les fans réside dans une collection comprenant également des dizaines de versions de jeux auparavant inédites ainsi que des exclusivités Sega Channel. Cette compilation inclut Garfield: Caught in the Act – The Lost Levels et The Flintstones, deux jeux autrefois considérés comme définitivement perdus.</text>
			<text lang="it">Sega Channel era un servizio di giochi online sviluppato da Sega per la console Sega Genesis, che fungeva da sistema di distribuzione dei contenuti. Lanciato il 12 dicembre 1994, Sega Channel fu offerto agli utenti da TCI e Time Warner Cable tramite servizi di televisione via cavo attraverso cavo coassiale. Era un servizio a pagamento che permetteva di accedere ai giochi Genesis online, giocare demo e utilizzare codici cheat.

Il servizio rimase attivo fino al 31 luglio 1998, continuando a operare per tre anni dopo l’uscita della console di nuova generazione Sega, la Sega Saturn. Nonostante le critiche per il tempismo del lancio e per l’elevato costo dell’abbonamento, Sega Channel è stato riconosciuto per le sue innovazioni nei contenuti scaricabili e per il suo impatto sui servizi di gioco online.

Di particolare interesse per gli appassionati è una collezione che include anche decine di versioni di giochi precedentemente inedite ed esclusive Sega Channel. Questa raccolta comprende Garfield: Caught in the Act – The Lost Levels e The Flintstones, due giochi che erano stati precedentemente considerati definitivamente perduti.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O Sega Channel foi um serviço de jogos online desenvolvido pela Sega para o console Sega Genesis, funcionando como um sistema de distribuição de conteúdo. Lançado em 12 de dezembro de 1994, o Sega Channel foi disponibilizado aos utilizadores pela TCI e pela Time Warner Cable através de serviços de televisão por cabo via cabo coaxial. Era um serviço pago que permitia aceder a jogos de Genesis online, jogar demos e utilizar códigos de trapaça.

O serviço esteve ativo até 31 de julho de 1998, continuando por três anos após o lançamento do console de nova geração da Sega, o Sega Saturn. Apesar das críticas ao momento do lançamento e ao elevado custo da assinatura, o Sega Channel foi reconhecido pelas suas inovações em conteúdo descarregável e pelo seu impacto no desenvolvimento dos serviços de jogos online.

De particular interesse para os fãs é uma coleção que inclui também dezenas de versões de jogos anteriormente inéditas e exclusivos do Sega Channel. Esta compilação inclui Garfield: Caught in the Act – The Lost Levels e The Flintstones, dois jogos que anteriormente eram considerados irremediavelmente perdidos.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
