<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
<!-- Original sonicretro -->
		<image name="sysart">
			<path>./../../_inc/arts/sonicretro.png</path>
			<path ifSubset="addons:yes">./../../../ckau-book-addons/_inc/arts/4K/sonicretro.png</path>
		</image>
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.499 0.43</pos>
			<size>0.18 0.23</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.2 0.23</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.25 0.23</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.13 0.23</size>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<pos>0.499 0.43</pos>
			<maxSize>0.205</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.225</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.275</maxSize>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>2021</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>Eukaryot</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>Sonic 3 A.I.R.</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextVariant">
			<text>Port</text>
			<text lang="pl">Port</text>
			<text lang="ru">Порт</text>
			<text lang="es">Puerto</text>
			<text lang="de">Hafen</text>
			<text lang="fr">Port</text>
			<text lang="it">Port</text>
			<text lang="pt">Porto</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>Sonic 3 A.I.R. (Angel Island Revisited) is a fan-made remake of Sonic 3 and Knuckles for PC (RSDK engine), created by Eukaryot. It enhances the original game with widescreen support, improved physics, controller support, and easy mod installation via a built-in menu.</text>
			<text lang="pl">Sonic 3 A.I.R. (Angel Island Revisited) to fanowski remake Sonic 3 and Knuckles na PC (silnik RSDK), stworzony przez Eukaryot. Ulepsza oryginalną grę dzięki obsłudze trybu panoramicznego, poprawionej fizyce, wsparciu dla kontrolerów oraz łatwej instalacji modów poprzez wbudowane menu.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Sonic 3 A.I.R. (Angel Island Revisited) — это фанатский ремейк Sonic 3 and Knuckles для ПК (движок RSDK), созданный Eukaryot. Он улучшает оригинальную игру поддержкой широкоформатного режима, улучшенной физикой, поддержкой контроллеров и простой установкой модов через встроенное меню.</text>
			<text lang="es">Sonic 3 A.I.R. (Angel Island Revisited) es un remake creado por fans de Sonic 3 and Knuckles para PC (motor RSDK), desarrollado por Eukaryot. Mejora el juego original con soporte para pantalla panorámica, física mejorada, compatibilidad con mandos y una sencilla instalación de mods mediante un menú integrado.</text>
			<text lang="de">Sonic 3 A.I.R. (Angel Island Revisited) ist ein Fan-Remake von Sonic 3 and Knuckles für PC (RSDK-Engine), erstellt von Eukaryot. Es erweitert das Originalspiel um Widescreen-Unterstützung, verbesserte Physik, Controller-Support und eine einfache Mod-Installation über ein integriertes Menü.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Sonic 3 A.I.R. (Angel Island Revisited) est un remake créé par des fans de Sonic 3 and Knuckles sur PC (moteur RSDK), développé par Eukaryot. Il améliore le jeu original avec le support du format large, une physique améliorée, la prise en charge des manettes et une installation facile des mods via un menu intégré.</text>
			<text lang="it">Sonic 3 A.I.R. (Angel Island Revisited) è un remake fan-made di Sonic 3 and Knuckles per PC (motore RSDK), creato da Eukaryot. Migliora il gioco originale con il supporto widescreen, una fisica migliorata, il supporto per i controller e una facile installazione delle mod tramite un menu integrato.</text>
			<text lang="pt">Sonic 3 A.I.R. (Angel Island Revisited) é um remake feito por fãs de Sonic 3 and Knuckles para PC (motor RSDK), criado por Eukaryot. Ele aprimora o jogo original com suporte a widescreen, física melhorada, suporte a controles e instalação fácil de mods através de um menu integrado.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
