<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.5 0.41</pos>
			<size>0.35 0.35</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.39 0.35</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.47 0.35</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.264 0.35</size>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<pos>0.5 0.41</pos>
			<maxSize>0.351</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.391</maxSize>
			<maxSize if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.47</maxSize>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>1997</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>ZUN</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>Touhou Project</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextVariant">
			<text>Collection</text>
			<text lang="pl">Kolekcja</text>
			<text lang="ru">Коллекция</text>
			<text lang="es">Recopilación</text>
			<text lang="fr">Collection</text>
			<text lang="it">Collezione</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>The Touhou Project, also known simply as Touhou, is a bullet hell shoot 'em up video game series created by independent Japanese doujin soft developer Team Shanghai Alice. The team's sole member, Jun'ya "ZUN" Ōta, has independently developed programming, graphics, writing, and music for the series, publishing 20 mainline games and 13 spin-offs since 1997. ZUN has also produced related print works and music albums, and collaborated with doujin developer Twilight Frontier on seven of the official spin-offs, six of which are fighting games.

The first five games were developed for the Japanese PC-98 computer, with the first, Highly Responsive to Prayers, released in August 1997; the series' signature danmaku mechanics were introduced in the second game, Story of Eastern Wonderland (also 1997). The release of Embodiment of Scarlet Devil in August 2002 marked a shift to Microsoft Windows. Numerous sequels followed, including several spin-offs departing from the traditional shoot 'em up format.

The Touhou Project is set in Gensokyo, a preternatural land sealed from the outside world and primarily inhabited by humans and yōkai, legendary creatures from Japanese folklore that are personified entirely as young girls and women in an anthropomorphic moe style. Reimu Hakurei, the miko of the Hakurei Shrine and the main character of the series, is often tasked with resolving supernatural "incidents" caused in and around Gensokyo; she is joined by Marisa Kirisame after the events of the second game.

The Touhou Project has become more particularly notable as a prominent source of Japanese doujin content, with the series spawning a vast amount of fan-made works such as artwork, music, print works, video games, and Internet memes. Because of this, it has gained a large cult following outside of Japan. The popularity of the series and its derivative works has been attributed in part to the few restrictions placed by ZUN on the use of his content. Unofficial works are frequently sold at fan conventions, including Comiket, where the franchise has frequently held the record for circle participation, and the official convention Reitaisai, where trial versions of the official games are typically distributed prior to release.</text>
			<text lang="it">The Touhou Project, noto anche semplicemente come Touhou, è una serie di videogiochi shoot ’em up bullet hell creata dal team doujin giapponese indipendente Team Shanghai Alice. L’unico membro del team, Jun'ya “ZUN” Ōta, ha sviluppato in modo indipendente la programmazione, la grafica, la sceneggiatura e la musica della serie, pubblicando 20 titoli principali e 13 spin-off dal 1997. ZUN ha inoltre prodotto opere cartacee e album musicali correlati e ha collaborato con lo sviluppatore doujin Twilight Frontier a sette spin-off ufficiali, sei dei quali sono picchiaduro.

I primi cinque giochi furono sviluppati per il computer giapponese PC-98, con il primo, Highly Responsive to Prayers, pubblicato nell’agosto 1997; le caratteristiche meccaniche danmaku della serie furono introdotte nel secondo gioco, Story of Eastern Wonderland (sempre nel 1997). L’uscita di Embodiment of Scarlet Devil nell’agosto 2002 segnò il passaggio a Microsoft Windows. In seguito furono pubblicati numerosi sequel, inclusi diversi spin-off che si allontanano dal formato shoot ’em up tradizionale.

The Touhou Project è ambientato a Gensokyo, una terra preternaturale sigillata dal mondo esterno e abitata principalmente da umani e yōkai, creature leggendarie del folklore giapponese rappresentate interamente come giovani ragazze e donne in uno stile moe antropomorfo. Reimu Hakurei, la miko del Santuario Hakurei e protagonista principale della serie, è spesso incaricata di risolvere “incidenti” soprannaturali che si verificano a Gensokyo e nei suoi dintorni; dopo gli eventi del secondo gioco viene affiancata da Marisa Kirisame.

The Touhou Project è diventato particolarmente noto come una delle principali fonti di contenuti doujin giapponesi, dando origine a una vastissima quantità di opere realizzate dai fan, come illustrazioni, musica, pubblicazioni cartacee, videogiochi e meme su Internet. Grazie a ciò, la serie ha ottenuto un ampio seguito di culto anche al di fuori del Giappone. La popolarità della serie e delle sue opere derivate è attribuita in parte alle poche restrizioni imposte da ZUN sull’uso dei suoi contenuti. Le opere non ufficiali vengono spesso vendute durante convention per fan, tra cui il Comiket, dove il franchise ha frequentemente detenuto il record per numero di circle partecipanti, e la convention ufficiale Reitaisai, dove le versioni di prova dei giochi ufficiali vengono solitamente distribuite prima dell’uscita.</text>
			<text lang="fr">The Touhou Project, également connu simplement sous le nom de Touhou, est une série de jeux vidéo de type shoot ’em up bullet hell créée par le développeur doujin japonais indépendant Team Shanghai Alice. L’unique membre de l’équipe, Jun'ya « ZUN » Ōta, a développé de manière indépendante la programmation, les graphismes, l’écriture et la musique de la série, publiant 20 jeux principaux et 13 spin-offs depuis 1997. ZUN a également produit des œuvres imprimées et des albums musicaux liés à la série, et a collaboré avec le développeur doujin Twilight Frontier sur sept spin-offs officiels, dont six jeux de combat.

Les cinq premiers jeux ont été développés pour l’ordinateur japonais PC-98, le premier, Highly Responsive to Prayers, étant sorti en août 1997 ; les mécaniques danmaku emblématiques de la série ont été introduites dans le deuxième jeu, Story of Eastern Wonderland (également en 1997). La sortie de Embodiment of Scarlet Devil en août 2002 a marqué le passage à Microsoft Windows. De nombreuses suites ont suivi, dont plusieurs spin-offs s’éloignant du format shoot ’em up traditionnel.

The Touhou Project se déroule à Gensokyo, un territoire surnaturel scellé du monde extérieur et principalement habité par des humains et des yōkai, des créatures légendaires du folklore japonais représentées entièrement comme de jeunes filles et femmes dans un style moe anthropomorphique. Reimu Hakurei, la miko du sanctuaire Hakurei et protagoniste principale de la série, est souvent chargée de résoudre des « incidents » surnaturels survenant à Gensokyo et dans ses environs ; après les événements du deuxième jeu, elle est rejointe par Marisa Kirisame.

The Touhou Project est devenu particulièrement remarquable en tant que source majeure de contenu doujin japonais, donnant naissance à une immense quantité d’œuvres créées par les fans, telles que des illustrations, de la musique, des publications, des jeux vidéo et des mèmes Internet. Grâce à cela, la série a acquis un large public de culte en dehors du Japon. La popularité de la série et de ses œuvres dérivées est en partie attribuée aux rares restrictions imposées par ZUN concernant l’utilisation de son contenu. Les œuvres non officielles sont fréquemment vendues lors de conventions de fans, notamment le Comiket, où la franchise a souvent détenu le record du nombre de cercles participants, ainsi que la convention officielle Reitaisai, où des versions d’essai des jeux officiels sont généralement distribuées avant leur sortie.</text>
			<text lang="de">The Touhou Project, auch einfach als Touhou bekannt, ist eine Bullet-Hell-Shoot-’em-up-Videospielreihe, die vom unabhängigen japanischen Dōjin-Entwickler Team Shanghai Alice geschaffen wurde. Das einzige Mitglied des Teams, Jun'ya „ZUN“ Ōta, entwickelte die Programmierung, Grafik, Texte und Musik der Serie eigenständig und veröffentlichte seit 1997 insgesamt 20 Haupttitel und 13 Spin-offs. ZUN produzierte außerdem begleitende Printwerke und Musikalben und arbeitete mit dem Dōjin-Entwickler Twilight Frontier an sieben offiziellen Spin-offs zusammen, von denen sechs Kampfspiele sind.

Die ersten fünf Spiele wurden für den japanischen PC-98-Computer entwickelt, wobei das erste, Highly Responsive to Prayers, im August 1997 erschien; die für die Serie typischen Danmaku-Mechaniken wurden im zweiten Spiel, Story of Eastern Wonderland (ebenfalls 1997), eingeführt. Die Veröffentlichung von Embodiment of Scarlet Devil im August 2002 markierte den Wechsel zu Microsoft Windows. Zahlreiche Fortsetzungen folgten, darunter mehrere Spin-offs, die sich vom traditionellen Shoot-’em-up-Format entfernten.

The Touhou Project spielt in Gensokyo, einem übernatürlichen Land, das von der Außenwelt abgeschottet ist und hauptsächlich von Menschen und Yōkai bewohnt wird – legendären Wesen aus der japanischen Folklore, die vollständig als junge Mädchen und Frauen in einem anthropomorphen Moe-Stil dargestellt werden. Reimu Hakurei, die Miko des Hakurei-Schreins und Hauptfigur der Serie, wird häufig damit beauftragt, übernatürliche „Vorfälle“ in und um Gensokyo zu lösen; nach den Ereignissen des zweiten Spiels schließt sich ihr Marisa Kirisame an.

The Touhou Project ist besonders als bedeutende Quelle japanischer Dōjin-Inhalte bekannt geworden und hat eine enorme Menge an von Fans erstellten Werken hervorgebracht, darunter Illustrationen, Musik, Printmedien, Videospiele und Internet-Memes. Dadurch hat die Serie auch außerhalb Japans eine große Kultanhängerschaft gewonnen. Die Popularität der Serie und ihrer Ableger wird teilweise den wenigen Einschränkungen zugeschrieben, die ZUN bei der Nutzung seiner Inhalte auferlegt hat. Inoffizielle Werke werden häufig auf Fan-Conventions verkauft, darunter die Comiket, bei der das Franchise oft den Rekord für die Anzahl teilnehmender Circles hielt, sowie die offizielle Convention Reitaisai, auf der üblicherweise Testversionen der offiziellen Spiele vor deren Veröffentlichung verteilt werden.</text>
			<text lang="es">The Touhou Project, también conocido simplemente como Touhou, es una serie de videojuegos shoot ’em up de tipo bullet hell creada por el desarrollador doujin japonés independiente Team Shanghai Alice. El único miembro del equipo, Jun'ya «ZUN» Ōta, ha desarrollado de forma independiente la programación, los gráficos, la escritura y la música de la serie, publicando 20 juegos principales y 13 spin-offs desde 1997. ZUN también ha producido obras impresas y álbumes musicales relacionados, y ha colaborado con el desarrollador doujin Twilight Frontier en siete spin-offs oficiales, seis de los cuales son juegos de lucha.

Los primeros cinco juegos fueron desarrollados para el ordenador japonés PC-98, siendo el primero, Highly Responsive to Prayers, lanzado en agosto de 1997; las mecánicas danmaku características de la serie se introdujeron en el segundo juego, Story of Eastern Wonderland (también en 1997). El lanzamiento de Embodiment of Scarlet Devil en agosto de 2002 marcó la transición a Microsoft Windows. Posteriormente se publicaron numerosas secuelas, incluidas varias spin-offs que se alejaron del formato shoot ’em up tradicional.

The Touhou Project se desarrolla en Gensokyo, una tierra sobrenatural sellada del mundo exterior y habitada principalmente por humanos y yōkai, criaturas legendarias del folclore japonés representadas íntegramente como chicas jóvenes y mujeres en un estilo moe antropomórfico. Reimu Hakurei, la miko del Santuario Hakurei y protagonista principal de la serie, suele encargarse de resolver “incidentes” sobrenaturales que ocurren en y alrededor de Gensokyo; tras los acontecimientos del segundo juego, se le une Marisa Kirisame.

The Touhou Project se ha vuelto especialmente notable como una fuente destacada de contenido doujin japonés, dando lugar a una enorme cantidad de obras creadas por fans, como ilustraciones, música, publicaciones impresas, videojuegos y memes de Internet. Gracias a ello, la serie ha ganado un gran seguimiento de culto fuera de Japón. La popularidad de la serie y de sus obras derivadas se atribuye en parte a las pocas restricciones impuestas por ZUN sobre el uso de su contenido. Las obras no oficiales se venden con frecuencia en convenciones de fans, incluido el Comiket, donde la franquicia ha ostentado en numerosas ocasiones el récord de participación de círculos, así como en la convención oficial Reitaisai, donde normalmente se distribuyen versiones de prueba de los juegos oficiales antes de su lanzamiento.</text>
			<text lang="ru">Touhou Project — серия компьютерных игр в жанре даммаку (скролл-шутер), созданная японской компанией Team Shanghai Alice, состоящей из одного человека, известного под псевдонимом ZUN. ZUN в одиночку производит графику, музыку и программный код своих игр.

Сюжет Touhou Project завязан вокруг странных феноменов, происходящих в Гэнсокё, вымышленной местности, населённой людьми и ёкаями, сверхъестественными существами. До событий в играх Гэнсокё был изолирован от внешнего мира магическим барьером. Протагонист серии, синтоистская жрица (мико) Рэйму Хакурэй, обеспечивает работоспособность барьера и сражается с враждебно настроенными ёкаями.

Первая игра серии вышла в 1996 году на японских компьютерах NEC PC-98, 6-я и все последующие части были выпущены на PC. На данный момент серия состоит из 28 игр, включая 10 спин-оффов.

Серия стала медиафраншизой, включающей в себя спин-оффы — файтинги, фанбуки, музыкальные CD, ранобэ и мангу в дополнение к основной серии. ZUN делает основные игры самостоятельно, однако за исполнение файтингов под его руководством отвечает студия Twilight Frontier, а иллюстрации для фанбуков, официальной манги и ранобэ выполняются другими художниками.

Благодаря разрешению создателя производить и продавать фанатские работы (в их числе фан-арт, додзинси, альбомы додзин-музыки и неофициальные игры, использующие вселенную и персонажей Touhou Project) и особенностям додзин-культуры, позволяющей распространять эти работы на Комикетах и иных мероприятиях, серия Touhou Project обрела популярность в Японии и в Интернет-среде, объяснимую лишь эффектом снежного кома, став уникальным в своём роде культурным феноменом.

В 2010 году серия «Touhou Project» была отмечена в игровом издании Книги рекордов Гиннесса, как «самая плодотворная серия любительских скролл-шутеров».</text>
			<text lang="pl">The Touhou Project, znany również po prostu jako Touhou, to seria gier wideo typu bullet hell shoot ’em up stworzona przez niezależnego japońskiego twórcę dōjin Team Shanghai Alice. Jedyny członek zespołu, Jun'ya „ZUN” Ōta, samodzielnie opracował programowanie, grafikę, scenariusz oraz muzykę serii, publikując od 1997 roku 20 głównych gier i 13 spin-offów. ZUN stworzył także powiązane publikacje drukowane i albumy muzyczne oraz współpracował z twórcą dōjin Twilight Frontier przy siedmiu oficjalnych spin-offach, z których sześć to gry walki.

Pierwsze pięć gier zostało opracowanych na japoński komputer PC-98, przy czym pierwsza z nich, Highly Responsive to Prayers, ukazała się w sierpniu 1997 roku; charakterystyczne dla serii mechaniki danmaku zostały wprowadzone w drugiej grze, Story of Eastern Wonderland (również w 1997 roku). Wydanie Embodiment of Scarlet Devil w sierpniu 2002 roku oznaczało przejście na system Microsoft Windows. Następnie ukazało się wiele kontynuacji, w tym liczne spin-offy odbiegające od tradycyjnego formatu shoot ’em up.

Akcja The Touhou Project rozgrywa się w Gensokyo — nadnaturalnej krainie odizolowanej od świata zewnętrznego i zamieszkanej głównie przez ludzi oraz yōkai, legendarne istoty japońskiego folkloru przedstawiane w całości jako młode dziewczęta i kobiety w antropomorficznym stylu moe. Reimu Hakurei, miko świątyni Hakurei i główna bohaterka serii, często zajmuje się rozwiązywaniem nadprzyrodzonych „incydentów” występujących w Gensokyo i jego okolicach; po wydarzeniach drugiej gry dołącza do niej Marisa Kirisame.

The Touhou Project stał się szczególnie znany jako jedno z najważniejszych źródeł japońskiej twórczości dōjin, dając początek ogromnej liczbie dzieł fanowskich, takich jak ilustracje, muzyka, publikacje drukowane, gry wideo oraz memy internetowe. Dzięki temu seria zyskała dużą kultową popularność poza Japonią. Popularność serii i jej pochodnych prac jest częściowo przypisywana niewielkiej liczbie ograniczeń nałożonych przez ZUN na wykorzystanie jego treści. Nieoficjalne prace są często sprzedawane na konwentach fanowskich, w tym na Comiket, gdzie franczyza wielokrotnie ustanawiała rekordy pod względem liczby uczestniczących kręgów, oraz na oficjalnym wydarzeniu Reitaisai, gdzie zazwyczaj rozpowszechniane są wersje demonstracyjne oficjalnych gier przed ich premierą.</text>
			<text lang="pt">The Touhou Project, também conhecido simplesmente como Touhou, é uma série de videogames shoot ’em up do tipo bullet hell criada pelo desenvolvedor doujin japonês independente Team Shanghai Alice. O único membro da equipe, Jun'ya “ZUN” Ōta, desenvolveu de forma independente a programação, os gráficos, a escrita e a música da série, publicando 20 jogos principais e 13 spin-offs desde 1997. ZUN também produziu obras impressas e álbuns musicais relacionados e colaborou com o desenvolvedor doujin Twilight Frontier em sete spin-offs oficiais, seis dos quais são jogos de luta.

Os primeiros cinco jogos foram desenvolvidos para o computador japonês PC-98, sendo o primeiro, Highly Responsive to Prayers, lançado em agosto de 1997; as mecânicas danmaku características da série foram introduzidas no segundo jogo, Story of Eastern Wonderland (também em 1997). O lançamento de Embodiment of Scarlet Devil em agosto de 2002 marcou a transição para o Microsoft Windows. Diversas sequências foram lançadas posteriormente, incluindo vários spin-offs que se afastam do formato tradicional de shoot ’em up.

The Touhou Project se passa em Gensokyo, uma terra sobrenatural selada do mundo exterior e habitada principalmente por humanos e yōkai, criaturas lendárias do folclore japonês representadas inteiramente como garotas jovens e mulheres em um estilo moe antropomórfico. Reimu Hakurei, a miko do Santuário Hakurei e personagem principal da série, é frequentemente encarregada de resolver “incidentes” sobrenaturais que ocorrem em Gensokyo e em seus arredores; após os eventos do segundo jogo, ela passa a ser acompanhada por Marisa Kirisame.

The Touhou Project tornou-se particularmente notável como uma importante fonte de conteúdo doujin japonês, dando origem a uma vasta quantidade de obras criadas por fãs, como ilustrações, músicas, publicações impressas, videogames e memes da Internet. Por isso, a série conquistou um grande público cult fora do Japão. A popularidade da série e de suas obras derivadas é atribuída em parte às poucas restrições impostas por ZUN ao uso de seu conteúdo. Obras não oficiais são frequentemente vendidas em convenções de fãs, incluindo a Comiket, onde a franquia frequentemente deteve o recorde de participação de círculos, e a convenção oficial Reitaisai, onde versões de teste dos jogos oficiais costumam ser distribuídas antes do lançamento.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>