<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<theme>
	<formatVersion>7</formatVersion>
	<view name="system">
		<image name="sysbg-video">
			<pos>0.5 0.4</pos>
			<size>0.16 0.22</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '16/10'">0.18 0.22</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '4/3'">0.22 0.22</size>
			<size if="${screen.ratio} == '21/9'">0.12 0.22</size>
		</image>
		<video name="videobox">
			<pos>0.5 0.404</pos>
			<maxSize>0.18</maxSize>
		</video>
		<text name="TextDate">
			<text>1977</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextManufacturer">
			<text>Tandy</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextName">
			<text>TRS-80</text>
		</text>
		<text name="TextDesc">
			<text>The TRS-80 (Tandy/Radio Shack, Z-80) is a home computer released in August 1977 by Tandy Corporation through their Radio Shack retail stores. It was one of the "1977 Trinity" of personal computers alongside the Apple II and Commodore PET, and was the best-selling personal computer from 1977 to roughly 1981.

The original Model I features a Zilog Z80 CPU at 1.774 MHz, 4 KB RAM (expandable to 48 KB), and a 64×16 character monochrome display with 128×48 block “graphics”. It came with a modified RCA black-and-white TV as a monitor, an integrated 53-key keyboard, and a cassette interface. The price started at a competitive $599.95. Despite being widely nicknamed the “Trash-80”, Tandy sold over 100,000 units in the first year — wildly exceeding their initial estimate of 3,000 — thanks to unparalleled retail distribution through 3,000+ Radio Shack stores across the US.</text>
			<text lang="pl">TRS-80 (Tandy/Radio Shack, Z-80) to komputer domowy wydany w sierpniu 1977 roku przez firmę Tandy Corporation i sprzedawany w sklepach sieci Radio Shack. Był jednym z tzw. „Trójcy 1977 roku” komputerów osobistych, obok Apple II i Commodore PET, oraz najlepiej sprzedającym się komputerem osobistym w latach 1977–około 1981.

Oryginalny Model I wyposażony był w procesor Zilog Z80 o częstotliwości 1,774 MHz, 4 KB pamięci RAM (rozszerzalnej do 48 KB) oraz monochromatyczny wyświetlacz tekstowy 64×16 znaków z blokową grafiką 128×48. W zestawie znajdował się zmodyfikowany czarno-biały telewizor RCA jako monitor, zintegrowana klawiatura z 53 klawiszami oraz interfejs kasetowy. Cena początkowa wynosiła konkurencyjne 599,95 USD. Pomimo przezwiska „Trash-80”, Tandy sprzedało ponad 100 000 egzemplarzy w pierwszym roku — znacznie przekraczając początkowe prognozy wynoszące 3 000 — dzięki szerokiej sieci ponad 3 000 sklepów Radio Shack w USA.</text>
			<text lang="ru">TRS-80 (Tandy/Radio Shack, Z-80) — это домашний компьютер, выпущенный в августе 1977 года компанией Tandy Corporation и продававшийся через сеть магазинов Radio Shack. Он входил в «троицу 1977 года» персональных компьютеров вместе с Apple II и Commodore PET и был самым продаваемым персональным компьютером с 1977 по примерно 1981 год.

Оригинальная модель Model I оснащалась процессором Zilog Z80 с частотой 1,774 МГц, 4 КБ оперативной памяти (расширяемой до 48 КБ) и монохромным текстовым дисплеем 64×16 символов с блочной графикой 128×48. В комплект входил модифицированный чёрно-белый телевизор RCA в качестве монитора, встроенная клавиатура на 53 клавиши и кассетный интерфейс. Начальная цена составляла конкурентные 599,95 доллара. Несмотря на распространённое прозвище «Trash-80», компания Tandy продала более 100 000 устройств в первый год — значительно превысив первоначальный прогноз в 3 000 — благодаря широкой сети из более чем 3 000 магазинов Radio Shack в США.</text>
			<text lang="es">El TRS-80 (Tandy/Radio Shack, Z-80) es un ordenador doméstico lanzado en agosto de 1977 por Tandy Corporation a través de sus tiendas Radio Shack. Fue uno de la “Trinidad de 1977” de ordenadores personales junto con el Apple II y el Commodore PET, y fue el ordenador personal más vendido desde 1977 hasta aproximadamente 1981.

El modelo original Model I cuenta con un procesador Zilog Z80 a 1,774 MHz, 4 KB de RAM (ampliables hasta 48 KB) y una pantalla monocroma de 64×16 caracteres con gráficos en bloques de 128×48. Incluía un televisor RCA en blanco y negro modificado como monitor, un teclado integrado de 53 teclas y una interfaz de casete. El precio inicial era de competitivos 599,95 dólares. A pesar de ser apodado “Trash-80”, Tandy vendió más de 100.000 unidades en su primer año, superando ampliamente la estimación inicial de 3.000, gracias a su extensa red de más de 3.000 tiendas Radio Shack en Estados Unidos.</text>
			<text lang="de">Der TRS-80 (Tandy/Radio Shack, Z-80) ist ein Heimcomputer, der im August 1977 von der Tandy Corporation über ihre Radio-Shack-Filialen veröffentlicht wurde. Er war Teil der sogenannten „1977 Trinity“ der Personal Computer zusammen mit dem Apple II und dem Commodore PET und war von 1977 bis etwa 1981 der meistverkaufte Personal Computer.

Das ursprüngliche Model I verfügt über einen Zilog Z80 Prozessor mit 1,774 MHz, 4 KB RAM (erweiterbar auf 48 KB) und ein monochromes Display mit 64×16 Zeichen sowie 128×48 Blockgrafik. Zum Lieferumfang gehörten ein modifizierter schwarz-weißer RCA-Fernseher als Monitor, eine integrierte Tastatur mit 53 Tasten und eine Kassettenschnittstelle. Der Einstiegspreis lag bei wettbewerbsfähigen 599,95 US-Dollar. Trotz des Spitznamens „Trash-80“ verkaufte Tandy im ersten Jahr über 100.000 Geräte — weit mehr als die ursprünglich erwarteten 3.000 — dank eines Vertriebsnetzes von über 3.000 Radio-Shack-Filialen in den USA.</text>
			<text lang="fr">Le TRS-80 (Tandy/Radio Shack, Z-80) est un ordinateur domestique lancé en août 1977 par Tandy Corporation via ses magasins Radio Shack. Il faisait partie de la « Trinité de 1977 » des ordinateurs personnels aux côtés de l’Apple II et du Commodore PET, et fut l’ordinateur personnel le plus vendu de 1977 à environ 1981.

Le modèle original Model I est équipé d’un processeur Zilog Z80 cadencé à 1,774 MHz, de 4 Ko de RAM (extensible à 48 Ko) et d’un affichage monochrome de 64×16 caractères avec des graphismes en blocs de 128×48. Il était livré avec un téléviseur noir et blanc RCA modifié comme moniteur, un clavier intégré de 53 touches et une interface cassette. Le prix de départ était de 599,95 dollars, très compétitif. Malgré le surnom « Trash-80 », Tandy a vendu plus de 100 000 unités dès la première année, dépassant largement les prévisions initiales de 3 000, grâce à un réseau de plus de 3 000 magasins Radio Shack aux États-Unis.</text>
			<text lang="it">Il TRS-80 (Tandy/Radio Shack, Z-80) è un computer domestico lanciato nell’agosto 1977 dalla Tandy Corporation attraverso i negozi Radio Shack. È stato uno della “Trinità del 1977” dei personal computer insieme all’Apple II e al Commodore PET, ed è stato il computer personale più venduto dal 1977 fino circa al 1981.

Il modello originale Model I è dotato di un processore Zilog Z80 a 1,774 MHz, 4 KB di RAM (espandibili fino a 48 KB) e un display monocromatico da 64×16 caratteri con grafica a blocchi 128×48. Includeva un televisore RCA in bianco e nero modificato come monitor, una tastiera integrata da 53 tasti e un’interfaccia a cassette. Il prezzo iniziale era di competitivi 599,95 dollari. Nonostante il soprannome “Trash-80”, Tandy vendette oltre 100.000 unità nel primo anno, superando di gran lunga la stima iniziale di 3.000, grazie a una rete di oltre 3.000 negozi Radio Shack negli Stati Uniti.</text>
			<text lang="pt">O TRS-80 (Tandy/Radio Shack, Z-80) é um computador doméstico lançado em agosto de 1977 pela Tandy Corporation através das lojas Radio Shack. Foi um dos integrantes da “Trindade de 1977” dos computadores pessoais, juntamente com o Apple II e o Commodore PET, sendo o computador pessoal mais vendido entre 1977 e aproximadamente 1981.

O modelo original Model I possui um processador Zilog Z80 a 1,774 MHz, 4 KB de RAM (expansível até 48 KB) e um ecrã monocromático de 64×16 caracteres com gráficos em blocos de 128×48. Incluía um televisor RCA a preto e branco modificado como monitor, um teclado integrado de 53 teclas e uma interface de cassete. O preço inicial era competitivo: 599,95 dólares. Apesar do apelido “Trash-80”, a Tandy vendeu mais de 100.000 unidades no primeiro ano, superando largamente a estimativa inicial de 3.000, graças à sua ampla rede de mais de 3.000 lojas Radio Shack nos Estados Unidos.</text>
		</text>
	</view>
</theme>
